<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE BlastOutput PUBLIC "-//NCBI//NCBI BlastOutput/EN" "http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/dtd/NCBI_BlastOutput.dtd">
<BlastOutput>
  <BlastOutput_program>psiblast</BlastOutput_program>
  <BlastOutput_version>PSIBLAST 2.9.0+</BlastOutput_version>
  <BlastOutput_reference>Alejandro A. Sch&amp;auml;ffer, L. Aravind, Thomas L. Madden, Sergei Shavirin, John L. Spouge, Yuri I. Wolf, Eugene V. Koonin, and Stephen F. Altschul (2001), &quot;Improving the accuracy of PSI-BLAST protein database searches with composition-based statistics and other refinements&quot;, Nucleic Acids Res. 29:2994-3005.</BlastOutput_reference>
  <BlastOutput_db>/home/oohnohnoh1/Desktop/ACADEMIA/Papermaking/OPTIMUS_BIND/PANDAS_TABLE/db/cdd_delta</BlastOutput_db>
  <BlastOutput_query-ID>Query_1</BlastOutput_query-ID>
  <BlastOutput_query-def>A &lt;unknown description&gt;</BlastOutput_query-def>
  <BlastOutput_query-len>52</BlastOutput_query-len>
  <BlastOutput_param>
    <Parameters>
      <Parameters_matrix>BLOSUM62</Parameters_matrix>
      <Parameters_expect>0.0005</Parameters_expect>
      <Parameters_gap-open>11</Parameters_gap-open>
      <Parameters_gap-extend>1</Parameters_gap-extend>
      <Parameters_filter>F</Parameters_filter>
    </Parameters>
  </BlastOutput_param>
<BlastOutput_iterations>
<Iteration>
  <Iteration_iter-num>1</Iteration_iter-num>
  <Iteration_query-ID>Query_1</Iteration_query-ID>
  <Iteration_query-def>A &lt;unknown description&gt;</Iteration_query-def>
  <Iteration_query-len>52</Iteration_query-len>
<Iteration_hits>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>1</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|349274</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd00024, CD_CSD, CHROMO (CHRromatin Organization Modifier) domains and chromo shadow domains.  Members of this group are chromodomains or chromo shadow domains; these are SH3-fold-beta-barrel domains of the chromo-like superfamily. Chromodomains lack the first strand of the SH3-fold-beta-barrel, this first strand is altered by insertion in the chromo shadow domains. The chromodomain is a conserved region of about 50 amino acids, found in a variety of chromosomal proteins, and which appears to play a role in the functional organization of the eukaryotic nucleus. The chromodomain is implicated in the binding, of the proteins in which it is found, to methylated histone tails and maybe RNA. Chromodomain-containing proteins include: i) those having an N-terminal chromodomain followed by a related chromo shadow domain, such as Drosophila and human heterochromatin protein Su(var)205 (HP1), and mammalian modifier 1 and 2; ii) those having a single chromodomain, such as Drosophila protein Polycomb (Pc), mammalian modifier 3, human Mi-2 autoantigen, and several yeast and Caenorhabditis elegans proteins of unknown function; iii) those having paired tandem chromodomains, such as mammalian DNA-binding/helicase proteins CHD-1 to CHD-4 and yeast protein CHD1; (iv) and elongation factor eEF3, a member of the ATP-binding cassette (ABC) family of proteins, that serves an essential function in the translation cycle of fungi. eEF3 is a soluble factor lacking a transmembrane domain and having two ABC domains arranged in tandem, with a unique chromodomain inserted within the ABC2 domain.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>349274</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>50</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>66.6254</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>161</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>2.05131e-17</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>2</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>49</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>1</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>49</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>32</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>39</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>1</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>49</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>YAVEKIIDRRVRKGMVEYYLKWKGYPETENTWEPENNL-DCQDLIQQYE</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>YEVEKILDHRVRKGKLEYLVKWKGYPPEENTWEPEENLTNAPELIKEYE</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>Y VEKI+D RVRKG +EY +KWKGYP  ENTWEPE NL +  +LI++YE</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>2</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|334050</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>pfam00385, Chromo, Chromo (CHRromatin Organisation MOdifier) domain.  </Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>334050</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>52</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>57.3806</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>137</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>7.49643e-14</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>2</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>49</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>1</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>50</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>31</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>37</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>2</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>50</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>YAVEKIIDRRVRKGMVEYYL-KWKGYPETENTWEPENN-LDCQDLIQQYE</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>YEVERILDHRKDKGGKEEYLVKWKGYPYDENTWEPEENLLDCPELIEEFE</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>Y VE+I+D R  KG  E YL KWKGYP  ENTWEPE N LDC +LI+++E</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>3</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|214605</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>smart00298, CHROMO, Chromatin organization modifier domain.  </Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>214605</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>55</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>51.6026</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>122</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>1.79444e-11</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>1</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>48</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>1</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>50</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>27</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>35</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>2</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>50</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>EYAVEKIIDRR-VRKGMVEYYLKWKGYPETENTWEPENN-LDCQDLIQQY</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>EYEVEKILDHRWKKKGELEYLVKWKGYSYSEDTWEPEENLLNCSKKLDNY</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>EY VEKI+D R  +KG +EY +KWKGY  +E+TWEPE N L+C   +  Y</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>4</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|349324</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd18968, chromodomain, CHROMO (CHRromatin Organization Modifier) domain; uncharacterized subgroup.  The chromodomain is a conserved region of about 50 amino acids, found in a variety of chromosomal proteins. The chromodomain is implicated in the binding, of the proteins in which it is found, to methylated histone tails and maybe RNA. A chromodomain may occur as a single instance, in a tandem arrangement, or followed by a related chromo shadow domain. Chromodomains belong to the chromo-like superfamily of SH3-fold-beta-barrel domains which includes chromo shadow domains and chromo barrel domains. Chromodomains differ from these in that they lack the first strand of the SH3-fold-beta-barrel. This first strand is altered by insertion in the chromo shadow domains, and chromo barrel domains are typical SH3-fold-beta-barrel domains with sequence similarity to the canonical chromo domain.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>349324</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>57</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>48.9062</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>115</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>2.47064e-10</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>1</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>48</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>1</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>55</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>26</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>35</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>7</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>55</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>EYAVEKIIDRRV------RKGMVEYYLKWKGYPETENTWEPENNLD-CQDLIQQY</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>EYEVEVILAARVVKDAESRKKGWKYLVKWAGYPDEENTWEPEESFDGCDDLLERF</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>EY VE I+  RV      RK   +Y +KW GYP+ ENTWEPE + D C DL++++</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>5</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|349334</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd18978, CD_DDE_transposase_like, chromodomain of Rhizopus microsporus putative DDE transposases, and similar proteins.  This subgroup includes the CHROMO (CHRromatin Organization Modifier) domain found in Rhizopus microsporus putative DDE transposases, and similar proteins. The chromodomain, is a conserved region of about 50 amino acids, found in a variety of chromosomal proteins, and implicated in the binding, of the proteins in which it is found, to methylated histone tails and maybe RNA. A chromodomain may occur as a single instance, in a tandem arrangement, or followed by a related chromo shadow domain.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>349334</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>52</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>48.1358</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>113</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>4.1339e-10</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>2</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>49</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>4</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>51</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>21</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>33</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>0</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>48</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>YAVEKIIDRRVRKGMVEYYLKWKGYPETENTWEPENNLDCQDLIQQYE</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>YEVEKIINHRGEKNRRKYLVKWKGYDDTDNSWVTQEDFNDKDMIDEYE</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>Y VEKII+ R  K   +Y +KWKGY +T+N+W  + + + +D+I +YE</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>6</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|349322</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd18966, chromodomain, CHROMO (CHRromatin Organization Modifier) domain; uncharacterized subgroup.  The chromodomain is a conserved region of about 50 amino acids, found in a variety of chromosomal proteins. The chromodomain is implicated in the binding, of the proteins in which it is found, to methylated histone tails and maybe RNA. A chromodomain may occur as a single instance, in a tandem arrangement, or followed by a related chromo shadow domain. Chromodomains belong to the chromo-like superfamily of SH3-fold-beta-barrel domains which includes chromo shadow domains and chromo barrel domains. Chromodomains differ from these in that they lack the first strand of the SH3-fold-beta-barrel. This first strand is altered by insertion in the chromo shadow domains, and chromo barrel domains are typical SH3-fold-beta-barrel domains with sequence similarity to the canonical chromo domain.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>349322</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>49</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>46.2098</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>108</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>1.86117e-09</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>2</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>49</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>1</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>48</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>21</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>32</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>0</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>48</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>YAVEKIIDRRVRKGMVEYYLKWKGYPETENTWEPENNLDCQDLIQQYE</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>YEVERILAERRDDGGKRYLVKWEGYPLEEATWEPEENIGDEELLKEWE</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>Y VE+I+  R   G   Y +KW+GYP  E TWEPE N+  ++L++++E</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>7</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|349320</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd18964, chromodomain, CHROMO (CHRromatin Organization Modifier) domain; uncharacterized subgroup.  The chromodomain is a conserved region of about 50 amino acids, found in a variety of chromosomal proteins. The chromodomain is implicated in the binding, of the proteins in which it is found, to methylated histone tails and maybe RNA. A chromodomain may occur as a single instance, in a tandem arrangement, or followed by a related chromo shadow domain. Chromodomains belong to the chromo-like superfamily of SH3-fold-beta-barrel domains which includes chromo shadow domains and chromo barrel domains. Chromodomains differ from these in that they lack the first strand of the SH3-fold-beta-barrel. This first strand is altered by insertion in the chromo shadow domains, and chromo barrel domains are typical SH3-fold-beta-barrel domains with sequence similarity to the canonical chromo domain.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>349320</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>54</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>36.965</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>84</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>1.21635e-05</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>2</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>49</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>1</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>53</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>21</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>29</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>5</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>53</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>YAVEKIIDRRVRK----GMVEYYLKWKGYPETENTWEPENNL-DCQDLIQQYE</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>FFVERIIGRRPSARDGPGKFLWLVKWDGYPIEDATWEPPENLGEHAKLIEDFE</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>+ VE+II RR       G   + +KW GYP  + TWEP  NL +   LI+ +E</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>8</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|349306</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd18659, CD2_tandem, repeat 2 of paired tandem chromodomains.  Repeat 2 of tandem CHRomatin Organization Modifier (chromo) domains, found in CHD (chromodomain helicase DNA-binding) proteins such as mammalian helicase DNA-binding proteins CHD1 to CHD9, and yeast protein CHD1. The CHD proteins belong to the SNF2 superfamily of ATP-dependent chromatin remodelers and contain two signature motifs: a pair of chromodomains located in the N-terminal region, and the SNF2-like ATPase domain located in the central region of the protein. CHD chromatin remodelers are important regulators of transcription and play critical roles during developmental processes. The N-terminal chromodomains of CHD1 have been shown to guard against sliding hexasomes. Mutations in the chromodomains of mouse CHD1 result in nuclear redistribution, suggesting that the chromodomain is essential for proper association with chromatin; also, deletion of the chromodomains in the Drosophila melanogaster CHD3-4 homolog impaired nucleosome binding, mobilization, and ATPase functions. A chromodomain is a conserved region of about 50 amino acids, found in a variety of chromosomal proteins, and which appears to play a role in the functional organization of the eukaryotic nucleus. The chromodomain is implicated in the binding, of the proteins in which it is found, to methylated histone tails and maybe RNA. A chromodomain may occur as a single instance, in a tandem arrangement, or followed by a related chromo shadow domain.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>349306</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>54</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>35.8094</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>81</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>2.79397e-05</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>4</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>47</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>5</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>47</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>21</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>27</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>3</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>45</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>VEKIIDRRVR-KGMVEYYLKWKGYPETENTWEPENNLDCQDLIQQ</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>VERIIAHREDDEGVTEYLVKWKGLPYDECTWESEE--DISDIFQE</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>VE+II  R   +G+ EY +KWKG P  E TWE E   D  D+ Q+</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>9</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|349276</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd18626, CD_eEF3, chromodomain-like insertion in an ATPase domain of elongation factor eEF3.  Eukaryotic elongation factor eEF3 (also known as EF-3, YEF3, and TEF3), a member of the ATP-binding cassette (ABC) family of proteins, is a ribosomal binding ATPase essential for fungal translation machinery. Until recently it was considered fungal-specific and therefore an attractive target for antifungal therapy; however, recent bioinformatics analysis indicates it may be more widely distributed among other unicellular eukaryotes, and translation elongation factor 3 activity has been demonstrated from a non-fungal species, Phytophthora infestans. eEF3 is a soluble factor lacking a transmembrane domain and having two ABC domains arranged in tandem, with a unique chromodomain inserted within the ABC2 domain. Chromodomain mutations in the ABC2 domain of eEF3 have been shown to reduce ATPase activity, but not ribosome binding. Thus, the chromodomain-like insertion is critical to eEF3 function. In addition to its elongation function, eEF3 has been shown to interact with mRNA in a translation independent manner, suggesting an additional, non-elongation function for this factor.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>349276</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>56</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>35.4242</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>80</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>5.13701e-05</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>3</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>47</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>3</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>50</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>18</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>27</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>3</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>48</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>AVEKIIDRRVRKGMVEYYLKWKGYPETENTWEPENNLD---CQDLIQQ</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>VIEKIVGRRKLKKSYEYEVKWKGMSSKDNSWIPREELEEMGFEKLVQE</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline> +EKI+ RR  K   EY +KWKG    +N+W P   L+    + L+Q+</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
</Iteration_hits>
  <Iteration_stat>
    <Statistics>
      <Statistics_db-num>29480</Statistics_db-num>
      <Statistics_db-len>6494941</Statistics_db-len>
      <Statistics_hsp-len>24</Statistics_hsp-len>
      <Statistics_eff-space>162047788</Statistics_eff-space>
      <Statistics_kappa>0.041</Statistics_kappa>
      <Statistics_lambda>0.267</Statistics_lambda>
      <Statistics_entropy>0.14</Statistics_entropy>
    </Statistics>
  </Iteration_stat>
</Iteration>
</BlastOutput_iterations>
</BlastOutput>

