<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE BlastOutput PUBLIC "-//NCBI//NCBI BlastOutput/EN" "http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/dtd/NCBI_BlastOutput.dtd">
<BlastOutput>
  <BlastOutput_program>psiblast</BlastOutput_program>
  <BlastOutput_version>PSIBLAST 2.9.0+</BlastOutput_version>
  <BlastOutput_reference>Alejandro A. Sch&amp;auml;ffer, L. Aravind, Thomas L. Madden, Sergei Shavirin, John L. Spouge, Yuri I. Wolf, Eugene V. Koonin, and Stephen F. Altschul (2001), &quot;Improving the accuracy of PSI-BLAST protein database searches with composition-based statistics and other refinements&quot;, Nucleic Acids Res. 29:2994-3005.</BlastOutput_reference>
  <BlastOutput_db>/home/oohnohnoh1/Desktop/ACADEMIA/Papermaking/OPTIMUS_BIND/PANDAS_TABLE/db/cdd_delta</BlastOutput_db>
  <BlastOutput_query-ID>Query_1</BlastOutput_query-ID>
  <BlastOutput_query-def>B &lt;unknown description&gt;</BlastOutput_query-def>
  <BlastOutput_query-len>91</BlastOutput_query-len>
  <BlastOutput_param>
    <Parameters>
      <Parameters_matrix>BLOSUM62</Parameters_matrix>
      <Parameters_expect>0.0005</Parameters_expect>
      <Parameters_gap-open>11</Parameters_gap-open>
      <Parameters_gap-extend>1</Parameters_gap-extend>
      <Parameters_filter>F</Parameters_filter>
    </Parameters>
  </BlastOutput_param>
<BlastOutput_iterations>
<Iteration>
  <Iteration_iter-num>1</Iteration_iter-num>
  <Iteration_query-ID>Query_1</Iteration_query-ID>
  <Iteration_query-def>B &lt;unknown description&gt;</Iteration_query-def>
  <Iteration_query-len>91</Iteration_query-len>
<Iteration_hits>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>1</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|276908</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd10582, TNFRSF14, Tumor necrosis factor receptor superfamily member 14 (TNFRSF14), also known as herpes virus entry mediator (HVEM).  TNFRSF14 (also known as herpes virus entry mediator or HVEM, ATAR, CD270, HVEA, LIGHTR, TR2) regulates T-cell immune responses by activating inflammatory, as well as inhibitory signaling pathways. HVEM acts as a receptor for the canonical TNF-related ligand LIGHT (lymphotoxin-like), which exhibits inducible expression, and competes with herpes simplex virus glycoprotein D for HVEM. It also acts as a ligand for the immunoglobulin superfamily proteins BTLA (B and T lymphocyte attenuator) and CD160, a feature distinguishing HVEM from other immune regulatory molecules, thus, creating a functionally diverse set of intrinsic and bidirectional signaling pathways. HVEM is highly expressed in the gut epithelium. Genome-wide association studies have shown that Hvem is an inflammatory bowel disease (IBD) risk gene, suggesting that HVEM could have a regulatory role influencing the regulation of epithelial barrier, host defense, and the microbiota. Mouse models have revealed that HVEM is involved in colitis pathogenesis, mucosal host defense, and epithelial immunity, thus acting as a mucosal gatekeeper with multiple regulatory functions in the mucosa. HVEM plays a critical role in both tumor progression and resistance to antitumor immune responses, possibly through direct and indirect mechanisms. It is known to be expressed in several human malignancies, including esophageal squamous cell carcinoma, follicular lymphoma and melanoma. HVEM network may therefore be an attractive target for drug intervention.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>276908</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>101</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>158.303</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>399</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>1.89489e-52</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>3</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>91</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>1</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>89</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>77</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>80</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>0</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>89</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>CKEDEYPVGSECCPKCSPGYRVKEACGELTGTVCEPCPPGTYIAHLNGLSKCLQCQMCDPAMGLRASRNCSRTENAVCGCSPGHFCIVQ</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>CKEDEYPVGSECCPKCSPGYRVKKACGELTGTVCEPCPPGTYTAHLNGLSKCLQCRVCDPAMGLVTRRNCSSTENTVCGCIPGHFCSAQ</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>CKEDEYPVGSECCPKCSPGYRVK+ACGELTGTVCEPCPPGTY AHLNGLSKCLQC++CDPAMGL   RNCS TEN VCGC PGHFC  Q</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>2</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|276910</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd13405, TNFRSF14_teleost, Tumor necrosis factor receptor superfamily member 14 (TNFRSF14) in teleost; also known as herpes virus entry mediator (HVEM).  This subfamily of TNFRSF14 (also known as herpes virus entry mediator or HVEM, ATAR, CD270, HVEA, LIGHTR, TR2) is found in teleosts, many of which are as yet uncharacterized. It regulates T-cell immune responses by activating inflammatory as well as inhibitory signaling pathways. HVEM acts as a receptor for the canonical TNF-related ligand LIGHT (lymphotoxin-like), which exhibits inducible expression, and competes with herpes simplex virus glycoprotein D for HVEM. It also acts as a ligand for the immunoglobulin superfamily proteins BTLA (B and T lymphocyte attenuator) and CD160, a feature distinguishing HVEM from other immune regulatory molecules, thus, creating a functionally diverse set of intrinsic and bidirectional signaling pathways. HVEM is highly expressed in the gut epithelium. Genome-wide association studies have shown that HVEM is an inflammatory bowel disease (IBD) risk gene, suggesting that HVEM could have a regulatory role influencing the regulation of epithelial barrier, host defense, and the microbiota. Mouse models have revealed that HVEM is involved in colitis pathogenesis, mucosal host defense, and epithelial immunity, thus acting as a mucosal gatekeeper with multiple regulatory functions in the mucosa. HVEM plays a critical role in both tumor progression and resistance to antitumor immune responses, possibly through direct and indirect mechanisms. It is known to be expressed in several human malignancies, including esophageal squamous cell carcinoma, follicular lymphoma, and melanoma. HVEM network may therefore be an attractive target for drug intervention. In Asian seabass, the up-regulation of differentially expressed TNFRSF14 gene has been observed.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>276910</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>111</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>82.0333</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>201</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>2.82782e-22</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>3</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>89</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>1</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>87</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>42</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>48</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>0</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>87</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>CKEDEYPVGSECCPKCSPGYRVKEACGELTGTVCEPCPPGTYIAHLNGLSKCLQCQMCDPAMGLRASRNCSRTENAVCGCSPGHFCI</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>CGPAEYEINGECCPMCPPGSRVSRHCTEDTSTSCVPCPDGTYMDEPNGLEKCFPCTNCDPGFGLRVKQGCTYTSDTVCEPLEGFYCI</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>C   EY +  ECCP C PG RV   C E T T C PCP GTY+   NGL KC  C  CDP  GLR  + C+ T + VC    G +CI</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>3</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|276931</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd15835, TNFRSF1B_teleost, Tumor necrosis factor receptor superfamily member 1B (TNFRSF1B) in teleost; also known as TNFR2.  This subfamily of TNFRSF1B (also known as TNFR2, type 2 TNFR, TNFBR, TNFR80, TNF-R75, TNF-R-II, p75, CD120b) is found in teleosts. It binds TNF-alpha, but lacks the death domain (DD) that is associated with the cytoplasmic domain of TNFRSF1A (TNFR1). It is inducible and expressed exclusively by oligodendrocytes, astrocytes, T cells, thymocytes, myocytes, endothelial cells, and in human mesenchymal stem cells. TNFRSF1B protects oligodendrocyte progenitor cells (OLGs) against oxidative stress, and induces the up-regulation of cell survival genes. While pro-inflammatory and pathogen-clearing activities of TNF are mediated mainly through activation of TNFRSF1A, a strong activator of NF-kappaB, TNFRSF1B is more responsible for suppression of inflammation. Although the affinities of both receptors for soluble TNF are similar, TNFRSF1B is sometimes more abundantly expressed and thought to associate with TNF, thereby increasing its concentration near TNFRSF1A receptors, and making TNF available to activate TNFRSF1A (a ligand-passing mechanism). Knockout studies in zebrafish embryos have shown that a signaling balance between TNFRSF1A and TNFRSF1B is required for endothelial cell integrity. TNFRSF1A signals apoptosis through caspase-8, whereas TNFRSF1B signals survival via NF-kB in endothelial cells. In goldfish (Carassius aurutus L.), TNFRSF1B expression is substantially higher than that of TNFRSF1 in tissues and various immune cell types. Both receptors are most robustly expressed in monocytes; mRNA levels of TNFRSF1B are lowest in peripheral blood leukocytes.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>276931</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>130</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>78.5666</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>192</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>1.45679e-20</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>6</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>90</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>11</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>96</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>41</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>50</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>1</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>86</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>DEYPVGSE-CCPKCSPGYRVKEACGELTGTVCEPCPPGTYIAHLNGLSKCLQCQMCDPAMGLRASRNCSRTENAVCGCSPGHFCIV</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>EYYNDGSNLCCSKCRPGTRLKTKCSETSDTVCEPCPSGQYSENWNYYPNCFSCPKCKERKGLQYAQNCSSTTNAVCVCKPGMYCIM</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>+ Y  GS  CC KC PG R+K  C E + TVCEPCP G Y  + N    C  C  C    GL+ ++NCS T NAVC C PG +CI+</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>4</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|276900</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd00185, TNFRSF, Tumor necrosis factor receptor superfamily (TNFRSF).  Members of TNFR superfamily (TNFRSF) interactions with TNF superfamily (TNFSF) ligands (TNFL) control key cellular processes such as differentiation, proliferation, apoptosis, and cell growth. Dysregulation of these pathways has been shown to result in a wide range of pathological conditions, including autoimmune diseases, inflammation, cancer, and viral infection. There are 29 very diverse family members of TNFRSF reported in humans: 22 are type I transmembrane receptors (single pass with the N terminus on extracellular side of the cell membrane) and have a clear signal peptide; the remaining 7 members are either type III transmembrane receptors (single pass with the N terminus on extracellular side of the membrane but no signal sequence; TNFR13B, TNFR13C, TNFR17, and XEDAR), or attached to the membrane via a glycosylphosphatidylinositol (GPI) linker (TNFR10C), or secreted as soluble receptors (TNFR11B and TNFR6B). All TNFRs contain relatively short cysteine-rich domains (CRDs) in the ectodomain, and are involved in interaction with the TNF homology domain (THD) of their ligands. TNFRs often have multiple CRDs (between one and six), with the most frequent configurations of three or four copies; most CRDs possess three disulfide bridges, but could have between one and four. Localized or genome-wide duplication and evolution of the TNFRSF members appear to have paralleled the emergence of the adaptive immune system; teleosts (i.e. ray-finned, bony fish), which possess an immune system with B and T cells, possess primary and secondary lymphoid organs, and are capable of adaptive responses to pathogens also display several characteristics that are different from the mammalian immune system, making teleost TNFSF orthologs and paralogs of interest to better understand immune system evolution and the immunological pathways elicited to pathogens.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>276900</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>87</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>60.8474</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>146</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>3.3002e-14</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>14</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>88</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>1</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>74</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>33</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>40</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>1</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>75</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>CCPKCSPGYRVKEACGELTGTVCEPCPPGTYIAHLNGLSKCLQCQMCDPAMGLRASRNCSRTENAVCGCSPGHFC</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>CCQRCPPGEYLSSDCTATTDTVCSPCPPGTYSESWNSLSKCLPCTTCGGGNQVEKTP-CTATDNRCCTCKPGFYC</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>CC +C PG  +   C   T TVC PCPPGTY    N LSKCL C  C     +  +  C+ T+N  C C PG +C</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>5</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|276911</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd13406, TNFRSF4, Tumor necrosis factor receptor superfamily member 4 (TNFRSF4), also known as  CD134 or OXO40.  TNFRSF4 (also known as OX40, ACT35, CD134, IMD16, TXGP1L) activates NF-kappaB through its interaction with adaptor proteins TRAF2 and TRAF5. It also promotes the expression of apoptosis inhibitors BCL2 and BCL2lL1/BCL2-XL, and thus suppresses apoptosis. It is primarily expressed on activated CD4+ and CD8+ T cells, where it is transiently expressed and upregulated on the most recently antigen-activated T cells within inflammatory lesions. This makes it an attractive target to modulate immune responses, i.e. TNFRSF4 (OX40) blocking agents to inhibit adverse inflammation or agonists to enhance immune responses. An artificially created biologic fusion protein, OX40-immunoglobulin (OX40-Ig), prevents OX40 from reaching the T-cell receptors, thus reducing the T-cell response. Some single nucleotide polymorphisms (SNPs) of its natural ligand OX40 ligand (OX40L, CD252), which is also found on activated T cells, have been associated with systemic lupus erythematosus.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>276911</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>142</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>55.0694</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>131</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>2.28663e-11</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>3</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>85</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>3</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>84</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>31</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>41</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>1</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>83</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>CKEDEYPVGSECCPKCSPGYRVKEACGELTGTVCEPCPPGTYIAHLNGLSKCLQCQMCDPAMGLRASRNCSRTENAVCGCSPG</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>CVGDTYPSGEKCCHECPPGEGMESRCTGTQDTVCSPCEPGFYNEAVN-YEPCKPCTQCNQRSGSEEKQKCTKTSDTVCRCRPG</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>C  D YP G +CC +C PG  ++  C     TVC PC PG Y   +N    C  C  C+   G    + C++T + VC C PG</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>6</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|276912</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd13407, TNFRSF5, Tumor necrosis factor receptor superfamily member 5 (TNFRSF5), also known as CD40.  TNFRSF5 (commonly known as CD40 and also as CDW40, p50, Bp50) is widely expressed in diverse cell types including B lymphocytes, dendritic cells, platelets, monocytes, endothelial cells, and fibroblasts. It is essential in mediating a wide variety of immune and inflammatory responses, including T cell-dependent immunoglobulin class switching, memory B cell development, and germinal center formation. Its natural immunomodulating ligand is CD40L, and a primary defect in the CD40/CD40L system is associated with X-linked hyper-IgM (XHIM) syndrome.  It is also involved in tumorigenesis; CD40 expression is significantly higher in gastric carcinomas and it is associated with the lymphatic metastasis of cancer cells and their tumor node metastasis (TNM) classification. Upregulated levels of CD40/CD40L on B cells and T cells may play an important role in the immune pathogenesis of breast cancer. Consequently, the CD40/CD40L system serves as a link between tumorigenesis, atherosclerosis, and the immune system, and offers a potential target for drug therapy for related diseases, such as cancer, atherosclerosis, diabetes mellitus, and immunological rejection.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>276912</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>161</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>55.4546</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>132</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>2.45009e-11</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>3</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>91</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>1</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>89</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>29</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>39</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>0</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>89</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>CKEDEYPVGSECCPKCSPGYRVKEACGELTGTVCEPCPPGTYIAHLNGLSKCLQCQMCDPAMGLRASRNCSRTENAVCGCSPGHFCIVQ</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>CREKQYLHNGRCCSLCPPGQKLVSDCTEATDTECLPCEEGEFQDTWNRERHCHQHRYCDPNLGLRVQTEGTAETDTTCTCQEGQHCTSE</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>C+E +Y     CC  C PG ++   C E T T C PC  G +    N    C Q + CDP +GLR     +   +  C C  G  C  +</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>7</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|276933</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd15837, TNFRSF26, Tumor necrosis factor receptor superfamily member 26 (TNFRSF26), also known as tumor necrosis factor receptor homolog 3 (TNFRH3).  TNFRSF26 (also known as tumor necrosis factor receptor homolog 3 (TNFRH3) or TNFRSF24) is predominantly expressed in embryos and lymphoid cell types, along with its closely related TNFRSF22 and TNFRSF23 orthologs, and is developmentally regulated. Unlike TNFRSF22/23, TNFRSF26 does not serve as a TRAIL decoy receptor; it remains an orphan receptor.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>276933</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>118</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>52.373</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>124</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>1.78843e-10</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>3</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>87</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>1</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>84</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>34</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>40</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>3</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>86</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>CKEDEYPVGSECCPKCSPGYRVKEACGELTGT-VCEPCPPGTYIAHLNGLSKCLQCQMCDPAMGLRASRNCSRTENAVCGCSPGHF</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>CGPGEYKSANLCCQLCPAGHYVSEPCQENHGVGECAPCEPGTFTAHPNGETSCFPCSQCRDDQEVVAE--CSATSDRQCQCKQGHF</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>C   EY   + CC  C  G+ V E C E  G   C PC PGT+ AH NG + C  C  C     + A   CS T +  C C  GHF</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>8</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|276905</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd10579, TNFRSF6, Tumor necrosis factor receptor superfamily member 6 (TNFRSF6), also known as fas cell surface death receptor (Fas).  TNFRSF6 (also known as fas cell surface death receptor (FasR) or Fas, APT1, CD95, FAS1, APO-1, FASTM, ALPS1A) contains a death domain and plays a central role in the physiological regulation of programmed cell death. It has been implicated in the pathogenesis of various malignancies and diseases of the immune system. The receptor interactions with the Fas ligand (FasL), allowing the formation of a death-inducing signaling complex that includes Fas-associated death domain protein (FADD), caspase 8, and caspase 10; autoproteolytic processing of the caspases in the complex triggers a downstream caspase cascade, leading to apoptosis. This receptor has also been shown to activate NF-kappaB, MAPK3/ERK1, and MAPK8/JNK, and is involved in transducing the proliferating signals in normal diploid fibroblast and T cells. Of the several alternatively spliced transcript variants, some are candidates for nonsense-mediated mRNA decay (NMD). Isoforms lacking the transmembrane domain may negatively regulate the apoptosis mediated by the full length isoform.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>276905</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>129</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>51.2174</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>121</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>5.78482e-10</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>2</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>88</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>9</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>97</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>33</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>41</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>2</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>89</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>SCKEDEYPVGSECCPKCSPGYRVKEACGELTGT-VCEPCPPGT-YIAHLNGLSKCLQCQMCDPAMGLRASRNCSRTENAVCGCSPGHFC</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>NCSEGLYRGGQFCCQPCPPGTRKAIDCTTNGGKPDCVPCTEGKEYTDKKHYSDKCRRCKICDEEHGLEVEKNCTRTQNTKCRCKSNFFC</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>+C E  Y  G  CC  C PG R    C    G   C PC  G  Y    +   KC +C++CD   GL   +NC+RT+N  C C    FC</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>9</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|276928</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd13423, TNFRSF6_teleost, Tumor necrosis factor receptor superfamily member 6 (TNFRSF6) in teleosts; also known as fas cell surface death receptor (FasR).  This subfamily of TNFRSF6 (also known as fas cell surface death receptor (FasR) or Fas; APT1; CD95; FAS1; APO-1; FASTM; ALPS1A) is found in teleosts. It contains a death domain and plays a central role in the physiological regulation of programmed cell death. In humans, it has been implicated in the pathogenesis of various malignancies and diseases of the immune system. The receptor interactions with the Fas ligand (FasL), allowing the formation of a death-inducing signaling complex that includes Fas-associated death domain protein (FADD), caspase 8, and caspase 10; autoproteolytic processing of the caspases in the complex triggers a downstream caspase cascade, leading to apoptosis. This receptor has also been shown to activate NF-kappaB, MAPK3/ERK1, and MAPK8/JNK, and is involved in transducing the proliferating signals in normal diploid fibroblast and T cells. In channel catfish and the Japanese rice fish, medaka, homologs of Fas receptor (FasR), as well as FADD and caspase 8, have been identified and characterized, and likely constitute the teleost equivalent of the death-inducing signaling complex (DISC). FasL/FasR are involved in the initiation of apoptosis and suggest that mechanisms of cell-mediated cytotoxicity in teleosts are similar to those used by mammals; presumably, the mechanism of apoptosis induction via death receptors was evolutionarily established during the appearance of vertebrates.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>276928</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>103</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>50.447</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>119</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>7.66931e-10</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>2</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>88</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>1</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>88</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>31</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>40</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>1</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>88</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>SCKEDEYPVGSECCPKCSPGYRVKEAC-GELTGTVCEPCPPGTYIAHLNGLSKCLQCQMCDPAMGLRASRNCSRTENAVCGCSPGHFC</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>SCEDGTYQHEGLTCCLCPAGQHVEKHCTNNGTDGECEACEDGTYNSHPNSLDSCEPCTSCDPNANLEVEERCTPSSDTVCRCKEGHYC</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>SC++  Y      C  C  G  V++ C    T   CE C  GTY +H N L  C  C  CDP   L     C+ + + VC C  GH+C</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>10</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|276902</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd10576, TNFRSF1A, Tumor necrosis factor receptor superfamily member 1A (TNFRSF1A), also known as TNFR1.  TNFRSF1A (also known as type I TNFR, TNFR1, DR1, TNFRSF1A, CD120a, p55) binds TNF-alpha, through the death domain (DD), and activates NF-kappaB, mediates apoptosis and activates signaling pathways controlling inflammatory, immune, and stress responses. It mediates signal transduction by interacting with antiapoptotic protein BCL2-associated athanogene 4 (BAG4/SODD) and adaptor proteins TRAF2 and TRADD that play regulatory roles. The human genetic disorder called tumor necrosis factor associated periodic syndrome (TRAPS), or periodic fever syndrome, is associated with germline mutations of the extracellular domains of this receptor, possibly due to impaired receptor clearance. TNFRSF1A polymorphisms rs1800693 and rs4149584 are associated with elevated risk of multiple sclerosis. Serum levels of TNFRSF1A are elevated in schizophrenia and bipolar disorder, and high levels are also associated with cognitive impairment and dementia. Patients with idiopathic recurrent acute pericarditis (IRAP), presumed to be an autoimmune process, have also been shown to carry rare mutations (R104Q and D12E) in the TNFRSF1A gene.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>276902</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>130</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>49.6766</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>117</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>2.50976e-09</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>8</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>87</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>8</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>88</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>29</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>37</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>1</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>81</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>YPVGSECCPKCSPGYRVKEAC-GELTGTVCEPCPPGTYIAHLNGLSKCLQCQMCDPAMGLRASRNCSRTENAVCGCSPGHF</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>HPNNNHCCTKCHKGTYLYNDCPGPGQDTVCRECENGTFTASENYLRKCLSCSRCRKEMGQVEISPCTVDQDTVCGCRKNQY</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>+P  + CC KC  G  +   C G    TVC  C  GT+ A  N L KCL C  C   MG      C+  ++ VCGC    +</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>11</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|276927</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd13422, TNFRSF5_teleost, Tumor necrosis factor receptor superfamily member 5 (TNFRSF5) in teleosts; also known as CD40.  TNFRSF5 (commonly known as CD40 and also as CDW40, p50, Bp50) is widely expressed in diverse cell types including B lymphocytes, dendritic cells, platelets, monocytes, endothelial cells, and fibroblasts. It is essential in mediating a wide variety of immune and inflammatory responses, including T cell-dependent immunoglobulin class switching, memory B cell development, and germinal center formation. Its natural immunomodulating ligand is CD40L, and a primary defect in the CD40/CD40L system is associated with X-linked hyper-IgM (XHIM) syndrome.  It is also involved in tumorigenesis; CD40 expression is significantly higher in gastric carcinomas and it is associated with the lymphatic metastasis of cancer cells and their tumor node metastasis (TNM) classification. Upregulated levels of CD40/CD40L on B cells and T cells may play an important role in the immune pathogenesis of breast cancer. Consequently, the CD40/CD40L system serves as a link between tumorigenesis, atherosclerosis, and the immune system, and offers a potential target for drug therapy for related diseases, such as cancer, atherosclerosis, diabetes mellitus, and immunological rejection. Salmon CD40 and CD40L are widely expressed, particularly in immune tissues, and their importance for the immune response is indicated by their relatively high expression in salmon lymphoid organs and gills.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>276927</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>161</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>48.1358</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>113</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>1.21605e-08</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>5</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>88</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>4</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>86</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>30</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>37</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>1</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>84</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>EDEYPVGSECCPKCSPGYRVKEACGELTGTVCEPCPPGTYIAHLNGLSKCLQCQMCDPAMGLRASRNCSRTENAVCGCSPGHFC</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>ETQYEKDGECCKMCGPGTRMSSDSGCLD-PQCQPCGEDEYQDKYTKENKCKRQPYCDPNKNFEISVNKSKTSRSVCKCKPGFHC</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>E +Y    ECC  C PG R+    G L    C+PC    Y       +KC +   CDP      S N S+T  +VC C PG  C</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>12</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|276901</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd10575, TNFRSF6B, Tumor necrosis factor receptor superfamily member 6B (TNFRSF6B), also known as decoy receptor 3 (DcR3).  The subfamily TNFRSF6B is also known as decoy receptor 3 (DcR3), M68, or TR6. This protein is a soluble receptor without death domain and cytoplasmic domain, and secreted by cells. It acts as a decoy receptor that competes with death receptors for ligand binding. It is a pleiotropic immunomodulator and biomarker for inflammatory diseases, autoimmune diseases, and cancer. Over-expression of this gene has been noted in several cancers, including pancreatic carcinoma, and gastrointestinal tract tumors. It can neutralize the biological effects of three tumor necrosis factor superfamily (TNFSF) members: TNFSF6 (Fas ligand/FasL/CD95L) and TNFSF14 (LIGHT) which are both involved in apoptosis and inflammation, and TNFSF15 (TNF-like molecule 1A/TL1A), which is a T cell co-stimulator and involved in gut inflammation. DcR3 is a novel inflammatory marker; higher DcR3 levels strongly correlate with inflammation and independently predict cardiovascular and all-cause mortality in chronic kidney disease (CKD) patients on hemodialysis. Increased synovial inflammatory cells infiltration in rheumatoid arthritis and ankylosing spondylitis is also associated with the elevated DcR3 expression. In cartilaginous fish, mRNA expression of DcR3 in the thymus and leydig, which are the representative lymphoid tissues of elasmobranchs, suggests that DcR3 may act as a modulator in the immune system. Interestingly, in banded dogfish (Triakis scyllia), DcR3 mRNA is strongly expressed in the gill, compared with human expression in the normal lung; both are respiratory organs, suggesting potential relevance of DcR3 to respiratory function.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>276901</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>163</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>45.4394</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>106</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>1.58016e-07</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>5</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>87</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>6</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>87</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>29</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>38</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>1</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>83</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>EDEYPVGSECCPKCSPGYRVKEACGELTGTVCEPCPPGTYIAHLNGLSKCLQCQMCDPAMGLRASRNCSRTENAVCGCSPGHF</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>KDDVTGESLTCDQCPPGTFVAKHCTRDRPTVCGPCPDLHYTQFWNYLEKCRYCNVFCTERQVE-KRQCNATHNRVCECKPGYY</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>+D+    S  C +C PG  V + C     TVC PCP   Y    N L KC  C +      +   R C+ T N VC C PG++</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>13</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|276921</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd13416, TNFRSF16, Tumor necrosis factor receptor superfamily member 16 (TNFRSF16), also known as p75 neurotrophin receptor (p75NTR) or CD271.  TNFRSF16 (also known as nerve growth factor receptor (NGFR) or p75 neurotrophin receptor (p75NTR or p75(NTR)), CD271, Gp80-LNGFR) is a common receptor for both neurotrophins and proneurotrophins, and plays a diverse role in many tissues, including the nervous system. It has been shown to be expressed in various types of stem cells and has been used to prospectively isolate stem cells with different degrees of potency. p75NTR owes its signaling to the recruitment of intracellular binding proteins, leading to the activation of different signaling pathways. It binds nerve growth factor (NGF) and the complex can initiate a signaling cascade which has been associated with both neuronal apoptosis and neuronal survival of discrete populations of neurons, depending on the presence or absence of intracellular signaling molecules downstream of p75NTR (e.g. NF-kB, JNK, or p75NTR intracellular death domain). p75NTR can also bind NGF in concert with the neurotrophic tyrosine kinase receptor type 1 (TrkA) protein where it is thought to modulate the formation of the high-affinity neurotrophin binding complex. On melanoma cell, p75NTR is an immunosuppressive factor, induced by interferon (IFN)-gamma, and mediates down-regulation of melanoma antigens. It can interact with the aggregated form of amyloid beta (Abeta) peptides, and plays an important role in etiopathogenesis of Alzheimer&apos;s disease by influencing protein tau hyper-phosphorylation. p75(NTR) is involved in the formation and progression of retina diseases; its expression is induced in retinal pigment epithelium (RPE) cells and its knockdown rescues RPE cell proliferation activity and inhibits RPE apoptosis induced by hypoxia. It can therefore be a potential therapeutic target for RPE hypoxia or oxidative stress diseases.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>276921</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>159</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>43.8986</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>102</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>5.03445e-07</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>2</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>87</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>2</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>85</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>31</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>44</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>4</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>87</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>SCKEDEYPVGSECCPKCSPGYRVKEACGELTGTVCEPCPPG-TYIAHLNGLSKCLQCQMCDPAMGLRASRNCSRTENAVCGCSPGHF</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>ACPSGQYTSSGECCEQCPPGEGVARPCGD-NQTVCEPCLDGVTFSDVVSHTEPCQPCTRCPGLMSMRAP--CTATHDTVCECAYGYY</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>+C   +Y    ECC +C PG  V   CG+   TVCEPC  G T+   ++    C  C  C   M +RA   C+ T + VC C+ G++</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>2</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>40.4318</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>93</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>9.1324e-06</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>15</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>80</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>96</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>159</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>25</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>32</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>2</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>66</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>CPKCSPGYRVKEACGELTGTVCEPCPPGTYIAHLNGLSKCLQCQMCDPAMGLRASRNCSRTENAVC</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>CTVCPPGQGVVQSCGPNQDTVCEACPEGTYSDEDSSTDPCLPCTVCE--DGEVELRECTPVSDTVC</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>C  C PG  V ++CG    TVCE CP GTY    +    CL C +C+   G    R C+   + VC</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>14</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|276915</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd13410, TNFRSF9, Tumor necrosis factor receptor superfamily member 9 (TNFRSF9), also known as CD137.  TNFRSF9 (also known as CD137, ILA, 4-1BB) plays a role in the immunobiology of human cancer where it is preferentially expressed on tumor-reactive subset of tumor-infiltrating lymphocytes. It can be expressed by activated T cells, but to a larger extent on CD8 than on CD4 T cells. In addition, CD137 expression is found on dendritic cells, follicular dendritic cells, natural killer cells, granulocytes and cells of blood vessel walls at sites of inflammation. It transduces signals that lead to the activation of NF-kappaB, mediated by the TRAF adaptor proteins. CD137 contributes to the clonal expansion, survival, and development of T cells. It can also induce proliferation in peripheral monocytes, enhance T cell apoptosis induced by TCR/CD3 triggered activation, and regulate CD28 co-stimulation to promote Th1 cell responses. CD137 is modulated by SAHA treatment in breast cancer cells, suggesting that the combination of SAHA with this receptor could be a new therapeutic approach for the treatment of tumors.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>276915</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>138</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>36.965</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>84</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>0.000164021</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>28</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>89</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>15</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>73</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>22</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>30</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>3</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>62</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>CGELTGTVCEPCPPGTYIAHLNGLSKCLQCQMCDPAMGLRASRNCSRTENAVCGCSPGHFCI</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>CGKNKDQTCIPCPPNSF-SSTGGQQTCDICRKCEGV--FRTKKPCSSTSNAECECVPGFHCL</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>CG+     C PCPP ++ +   G   C  C+ C+     R  + CS T NA C C PG  C+</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>15</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|276906</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd10580, TNFRSF10, Tumor necrosis factor receptor superfamily member 10 (TNFRSF10), includes TNFRSF10A (DR4), TNFRSF10B (DR5), TNFRSF10C (DcR1) and TNFRSF10D (DcR2).  TNFRSF10 family contains TNFRSF10A (also known as DR4, Apo2, TRAIL-R1, CD261), TNFRSF10B (also known as DR5, KILLER, TRICK2A, TRAIL-R2, TRICKB, CD262), TNFRSF10C (also known as DcR1, TRAIL-R3, LIT, TRID, CD263), and TNFRSF10D (also known as DcR2, TRUNDD, TRAIL-R4, CD264). Tumor necrosis factor-related apoptosis inducing ligand (TNFSF10/TRAIL) binds to all 4 receptors. DR4 (TRAIL-R1) and DR5 (TRAIL-R2) are membrane-bound and contain a death domain in their intracellular portion, which is able to transmit an apoptotic signal, thus often called death receptors. In contrast, DcR1 (TRAIL-R3), which lacks the complete intracellular portion and DcR2 (TRAIL-R4), which has a truncated cytoplasmic death domain, do not transmit an apoptotic signal, thus known as decoy receptors. Apoptosis mediated by DR4 and DR5 requires Fas (TNFRSF6)-associated via death domain (FADD), a death domain containing adaptor protein. Two transcript variants encoding different isoforms and one non-coding transcript have been found for TNFRSF10B/DR5. DcR1 appears to function as an antagonistic receptor that protects cells from TRAIL-induced apoptosis; it has been found to be a p53-regulated DNA damage-inducible gene. The expression of this gene is detected in many normal tissues but not in most cancer cell lines, which may explain the specific sensitivity of cancer cells to the apoptosis-inducing activity of TRAIL. DcR2 has been shown to play an inhibitory role in TRAIL-induced cell apoptosis. The membrane expression of all of these receptors (DR4, DR5, DcR1, and DcR2) is greater in normal endometrium (NE) than in endometrioid adenocarcinoma (EAC). In EAC patients, membrane expression of these receptors are not independent predictors of survival. DcR1 and DcR2 expression is critical in cell growth and apoptosis in cutaneous or uveal melanoma; DcR1 and DcR2 are frequently methylated in both, leading to loss of gene expression and melanomagenesis. On the other hand, DR4 and DR5 methylation is rare in cutaneous melanoma and frequent in uveal melanoma; their expression is wholly independent of the promoter methylation status. DcR1 and DcR2 genes are also reported to be hyper-methylated in prostate cancer. The TRAIL ligand, a potent and specific inducer of apoptosis in cancer cells, has been explored as a therapeutic drug; experimental data has shown that DR4 specific TRAIL variants are more efficacious than wild-type TRAIL in pancreatic cancer.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>276906</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>103</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>35.8094</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>81</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>0.000299367</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>15</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>88</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>2</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>69</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>28</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>31</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>8</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>75</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>CPKCSPGYRVKEACGELTGTVCEPCPPGT-YIAHLNGLSKCLQCQMCDPAMGLRASRNCSRTENAVCGCSPGHFC</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>CGLCPAGTYVSEDSGD-----CIPCKEGVDYTEHPNGLPSCLPCTVC--KSDEEELSPCTTTRNTECQCKPGTFC</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>C  C  G  V E  G+     C PC  G  Y  H NGL  CL C +C           C+ T N  C C PG FC</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
</Iteration_hits>
  <Iteration_stat>
    <Statistics>
      <Statistics_db-num>29480</Statistics_db-num>
      <Statistics_db-len>6494941</Statistics_db-len>
      <Statistics_hsp-len>57</Statistics_hsp-len>
      <Statistics_eff-space>163695754</Statistics_eff-space>
      <Statistics_kappa>0.041</Statistics_kappa>
      <Statistics_lambda>0.267</Statistics_lambda>
      <Statistics_entropy>0.14</Statistics_entropy>
    </Statistics>
  </Iteration_stat>
</Iteration>
</BlastOutput_iterations>
</BlastOutput>

