<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE BlastOutput PUBLIC "-//NCBI//NCBI BlastOutput/EN" "http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/dtd/NCBI_BlastOutput.dtd">
<BlastOutput>
  <BlastOutput_program>psiblast</BlastOutput_program>
  <BlastOutput_version>PSIBLAST 2.9.0+</BlastOutput_version>
  <BlastOutput_reference>Alejandro A. Sch&amp;auml;ffer, L. Aravind, Thomas L. Madden, Sergei Shavirin, John L. Spouge, Yuri I. Wolf, Eugene V. Koonin, and Stephen F. Altschul (2001), &quot;Improving the accuracy of PSI-BLAST protein database searches with composition-based statistics and other refinements&quot;, Nucleic Acids Res. 29:2994-3005.</BlastOutput_reference>
  <BlastOutput_db>/home/oohnohnoh1/Desktop/ACADEMIA/Papermaking/OPTIMUS_BIND/PANDAS_TABLE/db/cdd_delta</BlastOutput_db>
  <BlastOutput_query-ID>Query_1</BlastOutput_query-ID>
  <BlastOutput_query-def>C &lt;unknown description&gt;</BlastOutput_query-def>
  <BlastOutput_query-len>69</BlastOutput_query-len>
  <BlastOutput_param>
    <Parameters>
      <Parameters_matrix>BLOSUM62</Parameters_matrix>
      <Parameters_expect>0.0005</Parameters_expect>
      <Parameters_gap-open>11</Parameters_gap-open>
      <Parameters_gap-extend>1</Parameters_gap-extend>
      <Parameters_filter>F</Parameters_filter>
    </Parameters>
  </BlastOutput_param>
<BlastOutput_iterations>
<Iteration>
  <Iteration_iter-num>1</Iteration_iter-num>
  <Iteration_query-ID>Query_1</Iteration_query-ID>
  <Iteration_query-def>C &lt;unknown description&gt;</Iteration_query-def>
  <Iteration_query-len>69</Iteration_query-len>
<Iteration_hits>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>1</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|212810</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd11877, SH3_PIX, Src Homology 3 domain of Pak Interactive eXchange factors.  PIX proteins are Rho guanine nucleotide exchange factors (GEFs), which activate small GTPases by exchanging bound GDP for free GTP. They act as GEFs for both Cdc42 and Rac 1, and have been implicated in cell motility, adhesion, neurite outgrowth, and cell polarity. Vertebrates contain two proteins from the PIX subfamily, alpha-PIX and beta-PIX. Alpha-PIX, also called ARHGEF6, is localized in dendritic spines where it regulates spine morphogenesis. Mutations in the ARHGEF6 gene cause X-linked intellectual disability in humans. Beta-PIX play roles in regulating neuroendocrine exocytosis, focal adhesion maturation, cell migration, synaptic vesicle localization, and insulin secretion. PIX proteins contain an N-terminal SH3 domain followed by RhoGEF (also called Dbl-homologous or DH) and Pleckstrin Homology (PH) domains, and a C-terminal leucine-zipper domain for dimerization. The SH3 domain of PIX binds to an atypical PxxxPR motif in p21-activated kinases (PAKs) with high affinity. The binding of PAKs to PIX facilitate the localization of PAKs to focal complexes and also localizes PAKs to PIX targets Cdc43 and Rac, leading to the activation of PAKs. SH3 domains are protein interaction domains that bind to proline-rich ligands with moderate affinity and selectivity, preferentially to PxxP motifs. They play versatile and diverse roles in the cell including the regulation of enzymes, changing the subcellular localization of signaling pathway components, and mediating the formation of multiprotein complex assemblies.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>212810</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>53</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>33.8834</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>76</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>0.000346473</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>27</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>66</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>16</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>52</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>17</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>22</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>3</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>40</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>LRLNPGDIVELTKAEAEHNWWEGRNTATNEVGWFPCNRVH</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>LSFDKGDIITVTQV-VEGGWWEG--TLNGKTGWFPSNYVK</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>L  + GDI+ +T+   E  WWEG  T   + GWFP N V </Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>2</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|212697</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd11763, SH3_SNX9_like, Src Homology 3 domain of Sorting Nexin 9 and similar proteins.  Sorting nexins (SNXs) are Phox homology (PX) domain containing proteins that are involved in regulating membrane traffic and protein sorting in the endosomal system. SNXs differ from each other in their lipid-binding specificity, subcellular localization and specific function in the endocytic pathway. This subfamily consists of SH3 domain containing SNXs including SNX9, SNX18, SNX33, and similar proteins. SNX9 is localized to plasma membrane endocytic sites and acts primarily in clathrin-mediated endocytosis, while SNX18 is localized to peripheral endosomal structures, and acts in a trafficking pathway that is clathrin-independent but relies on AP-1 and PACS1. SH3 domains are protein interaction domains that bind to proline-rich ligands with moderate affinity and selectivity, preferentially to PxxP motifs. They play versatile and diverse roles in the cell including the regulation of enzymes, changing the subcellular localization of signaling pathway components, and mediating the formation of multiprotein complex assemblies.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>212697</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>55</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>33.4982</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>75</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>0.000467869</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>27</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>66</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>16</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>54</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>15</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>23</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>1</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>40</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>LRLNPGDIVELTKAEAEHNWWEGRNTATNEVGWFPCNRVH</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>LSLRAGEVLTITRQDVGDGWLEGRNS-RGEVGLFPSSYVE</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>L L  G+++ +T+ +    W EGRN+   EVG FP + V </Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
</Iteration_hits>
  <Iteration_stat>
    <Statistics>
      <Statistics_db-num>29480</Statistics_db-num>
      <Statistics_db-len>6494941</Statistics_db-len>
      <Statistics_hsp-len>39</Statistics_hsp-len>
      <Statistics_eff-space>160356630</Statistics_eff-space>
      <Statistics_kappa>0.041</Statistics_kappa>
      <Statistics_lambda>0.267</Statistics_lambda>
      <Statistics_entropy>0.14</Statistics_entropy>
    </Statistics>
  </Iteration_stat>
</Iteration>
</BlastOutput_iterations>
</BlastOutput>

