<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE BlastOutput PUBLIC "-//NCBI//NCBI BlastOutput/EN" "http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/dtd/NCBI_BlastOutput.dtd">
<BlastOutput>
  <BlastOutput_program>psiblast</BlastOutput_program>
  <BlastOutput_version>PSIBLAST 2.9.0+</BlastOutput_version>
  <BlastOutput_reference>Alejandro A. Sch&amp;auml;ffer, L. Aravind, Thomas L. Madden, Sergei Shavirin, John L. Spouge, Yuri I. Wolf, Eugene V. Koonin, and Stephen F. Altschul (2001), &quot;Improving the accuracy of PSI-BLAST protein database searches with composition-based statistics and other refinements&quot;, Nucleic Acids Res. 29:2994-3005.</BlastOutput_reference>
  <BlastOutput_db>/home/oohnohnoh1/Desktop/ACADEMIA/Papermaking/OPTIMUS_BIND/PANDAS_TABLE/db/cdd_delta</BlastOutput_db>
  <BlastOutput_query-ID>Query_1</BlastOutput_query-ID>
  <BlastOutput_query-def>B &lt;unknown description&gt;</BlastOutput_query-def>
  <BlastOutput_query-len>120</BlastOutput_query-len>
  <BlastOutput_param>
    <Parameters>
      <Parameters_matrix>BLOSUM62</Parameters_matrix>
      <Parameters_expect>0.0005</Parameters_expect>
      <Parameters_gap-open>11</Parameters_gap-open>
      <Parameters_gap-extend>1</Parameters_gap-extend>
      <Parameters_filter>F</Parameters_filter>
    </Parameters>
  </BlastOutput_param>
<BlastOutput_iterations>
<Iteration>
  <Iteration_iter-num>1</Iteration_iter-num>
  <Iteration_query-ID>Query_1</Iteration_query-ID>
  <Iteration_query-def>B &lt;unknown description&gt;</Iteration_query-def>
  <Iteration_query-len>120</Iteration_query-len>
<Iteration_hits>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>1</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|143285</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd05877, Ig_LP_like, Immunoglobulin (Ig)-like domain of human cartilage link protein (LP).  Ig_LP_like: immunoglobulin (Ig)-like domain similar to that that found in human cartilage link protein (LP), also called hyaluronan and proteoglycan link protein. In cartilage, chondroitin-keratan sulfate proteoglycan (CSPG), aggrecan, forms cartilage link protein stabilized aggregates with hyaluronan (HA). These aggregates contribute to the tissue&apos;s load bearing properties. Aggregates having other CSPGs substituting for aggrecan may contribute to the structural integrity of many different tissues. Members of the vertebrate HPLN (hyaluronan/HA and proteoglycan binding link) protein family are physically linked adjacent to CSPG genes.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>143285</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>106</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>45.4394</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>106</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>1.32769e-07</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>15</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>104</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>1</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>87</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>30</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>51</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>11</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>94</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>KGETAYLPCKFTLSPEDQGP--LDIEWLISPADNQKVDQVII-LYSGDKIYDDYYPDLKGRVHFT-SNDLKSGDASINVTNLQLSDIGTYQCKV</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>RGGNVTLPCRYHYEPELSAPRKIRVKWTKLESDYLKEEDVLVAIGTRHKSYGSY----QGRVFLRRAHDL---DASLVITDLRLEDYGRYRCEV</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>+G    LPC++   PE   P  + ++W    +D  K + V++ + +  K Y  Y    +GRV    ++DL   DAS+ +T+L+L D G Y+C+V</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>2</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|319291</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd05713, Ig_MOG_like, Immunoglobulin (Ig)-like domain of myelin oligodendrocyte glycoprotein (MOG).  Ig_MOG_like: immunoglobulin (Ig)-like domain of myelin oligodendrocyte glycoprotein (MOG). MOG, a minor component of the myelin sheath, is an important CNS-specific autoantigen, linked to the pathogenesis of multiple sclerosis (MS) and experimental autoimmune encephalomyelitis (EAE). It is a transmembrane protein having an extracellular Ig domain. MOG is expressed in the CNS on the outermost lamellae of the myelin sheath, and on the surface of oligodendrocytes, and may participate in the completion, compaction, and/or maintenance of myelin. This group also includes butyrophilin (BTN). BTN is the most abundant protein in bovine milk-fat globule membrane (MFGM).</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>319291</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>100</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>44.669</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>104</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>2.53061e-07</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>16</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>102</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>1</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>82</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>26</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>43</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>9</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>89</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>GETAYLPCKFTLSPEDQGP-LDIEWLISPADNQKVDQVIILYS-GDKIYDDYYPDLKGRVHFTSNDLKSGDASINVTNLQLSDIGTYQC</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>GEDAELPCH--LSPKMSAEHMEVRWFRS-----QFSPVVHLYRDGQDQYEEQMPEYRGRTELLKDAIAEGSVALRIHNVRASDEGQYTC</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>GE A LPC   LSP+     +++ W  S     +   V+ LY  G   Y++  P+ +GR     + +  G  ++ + N++ SD G Y C</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>3</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|319336</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd16087, IgV_CD86, Immunoglobulin variable domain (IgV) in CD86.  Glycoproteins B7-1 (CD80) and B7-2 (CD86) are expressed on antigen-presenting cells and deliver the co-stimulatory signal through CD28 and CTLA-4 (CD152) on T cells.  Signalling through CD28 augments the T-cell response, whereas CTLA-4 signalling attenuates it. The CTLA-4 and B7-2 monomers are both two-layer beta-sandwiches that display the chain topology characteristic of the immunoglobulin variable (V-type) domains present in antigen receptors. The front and back sheets of B7-2 are composed of AGFCC&apos;C&quot; and BED strands, respectively. Members of the IgV family are components of immunoglobulin (Ig) and T cell receptors. The basic structure of Ig molecules is a tetramer of two light chains and two heavy chains linked by disulfide bonds. In Ig, each chain is composed of one variable domain (IgV) and one or more constant domains (IgC); these names reflect the fact that the variability in sequences is higher in the variable domain than in the constant domain. Within the variable domain, there are regions of even more variability called the hypervariable or complementarity-determining regions (CDRs) which are responsible for antigen binding. A predominant feature of most Ig domains is the disulfide bridge connecting 2 beta-sheets with a tryptophan residue packed against the disulfide bond.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>319336</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>106</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>40.817</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>94</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>7.6212e-06</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>11</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>108</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>1</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>90</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>30</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>50</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>10</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>99</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>IEKAKGETAYLPCKFTLSPEDQGPLDIEWLISPADNQKVDQVIILYSGDKIYDDYYPDLKGRVHFTSNDLKSGDASINVTNLQLSDIGTYQCKV-KKAP</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>IQAYFNETAYLPCQFK-NPQN---ISLSELVVFWQDQKKLVLYELYLGKEKLDNVNSKYIGRTSFDQENW-----TLQLHNVQIKDQGTYQCFIHHKSP</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>I+    ETAYLPC+F  +P++   + +  L+    +QK   +  LY G +  D+      GR  F   +      ++ + N+Q+ D GTYQC +  K+P</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>4</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|336766</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>pfam07686, V-set, Immunoglobulin V-set domain.  This domain is found in antibodies as well as neural protein P0 and CTL4 amongst others.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>336766</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>109</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>37.7354</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>86</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>0.000122403</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>6</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>120</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>2</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>109</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>36</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>52</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>11</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>117</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>TPEEMIEKAKGETAYLPCKFTLSPEDQGPLDIEWLISPADNQKVDQVIILYSGDKIYDDYYPDLKGRVHFT-SNDLKSGDASINVTNLQLSDIGTYQCKVK-KAPGVANKKIHLVVL</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>TPRE-VTVAEGGSVTLPCTYSSSMSEGS-TSVYWYRQPPG--KGPEELIAY-----YSNKSPEGKKKGRFSLRGDPSNSDFSLTIQNLTPSDSGTYFCAVGPNGEGVFGKGTRLTVL</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>TP E +  A+G +  LPC ++ S  +     + W   P    K  + +I Y     Y +  P+ K +  F+   D  + D S+ + NL  SD GTY C V     GV  K   L VL</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>5</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|319275</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd00099, IgV, Immunoglobulin variable domain (IgV).  IgV: Immunoglobulin variable domain (IgV). Members of the IgV family are components of immunoglobulin (Ig) and T cell receptors. The basic structure of Ig molecules is a tetramer of two light chains and two heavy chains linked by disulfide bonds. In Ig, each chain is composed of one variable domain (IgV) and one or more constant domains (IgC); these names reflect the fact that the variability in sequences is higher in the variable domain than in the constant domain. Within the variable domain, there are regions of even more variability called the hypervariable or complementarity-determining regions (CDRs) which are responsible for antigen binding. A predominant feature of most Ig domains is the disulfide bridge connecting 2 beta-sheets with a tryptophan residue packed against the disulfide bond.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>319275</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>103</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>36.1946</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>82</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>0.000378324</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>67</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>116</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>47</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>95</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>18</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>26</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>1</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>50</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>PDLKGRVHFTSNDLKSGDASINVTNLQLSDIGTYQCKVKKAPGVANKKIH</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>PGIPGRFSGTRNGGSS-SFSLTISNLRPEDSGTYYCAVSEGPGGGDKLVF</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>P + GR   T N   S   S+ ++NL+  D GTY C V + PG  +K + </Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>6</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|319295</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd05718, Ig1_PVR_like, First immunoglobulin (Ig) domain of poliovirus receptor (PVR, also known as CD155) and similar proteins.  Ig1_PVR_like: domain similar to the first immunoglobulin (Ig) domain of poliovirus receptor (PVR, also known as CD155). Poliovirus (PV) binds to its cellular receptor (PVR/CD155) to initiate infection. CD155 is a membrane-anchored, single-span glycoprotein; its extracellular region has three Ig-like domains. There are four different isotypes of CD155 (referred to as alpha, beta, gamma, and delta), that result from alternate splicing of the CD155 mRNA, and have identical extracellular domains. CD155-beta and - gamma, are secreted, CD155-alpha and delta are membrane-bound and function as PV receptors. The virus recognition site is contained in the amino-terminal domain, D1. Having the virus attachment site on the receptor distal from the plasma membrane, may be important for successful initiation of infection of cells by the virus. CD155 binds in the poliovirus &quot;canyon&quot; with a footprint similar to that of the intercellular adhesion molecule-1 receptor on human rhinoviruses. This group also includes the first Ig-like domain of nectin-1 (also known as poliovirus receptor related protein(PVRL)1; CD111), nectin-3 (also known as PVRL 3), nectin-4 (also known as PVRL4; LNIR receptor)and DNAX accessory molecule 1 (DNAM-1; CD226).</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>319295</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>99</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>36.1946</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>82</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>0.000389769</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>21</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>120</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>5</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>99</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>29</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>47</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>7</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>101</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>LPCKFTLSPEDQGPLDIEWLISPADNQKVDQVIILYSGDKIYDDYYPDLKGRVHFTSNDLKSGDASINVTNLQLSDIGTYQCKVKKAP-GVANKKIHLVVL</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>LPCSLT-SPGTVQITQVTWMKIGGESSQNIAVFHPQFGPSVPNPY---VKGRVAFLNSSLN--NATLRISNLRVEDEGNYICEFATFPQGNRQGVTWLVVL</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>LPC  T SP       + W+    ++ +   V     G  + + Y   +KGRV F ++ L   +A++ ++NL++ D G Y C+    P G       LVVL</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
</Iteration_hits>
  <Iteration_stat>
    <Statistics>
      <Statistics_db-num>29480</Statistics_db-num>
      <Statistics_db-len>6494941</Statistics_db-len>
      <Statistics_hsp-len>81</Statistics_hsp-len>
      <Statistics_eff-space>160175379</Statistics_eff-space>
      <Statistics_kappa>0.041</Statistics_kappa>
      <Statistics_lambda>0.267</Statistics_lambda>
      <Statistics_entropy>0.14</Statistics_entropy>
    </Statistics>
  </Iteration_stat>
</Iteration>
</BlastOutput_iterations>
</BlastOutput>

