<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE BlastOutput PUBLIC "-//NCBI//NCBI BlastOutput/EN" "http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/dtd/NCBI_BlastOutput.dtd">
<BlastOutput>
  <BlastOutput_program>psiblast</BlastOutput_program>
  <BlastOutput_version>PSIBLAST 2.9.0+</BlastOutput_version>
  <BlastOutput_reference>Alejandro A. Sch&amp;auml;ffer, L. Aravind, Thomas L. Madden, Sergei Shavirin, John L. Spouge, Yuri I. Wolf, Eugene V. Koonin, and Stephen F. Altschul (2001), &quot;Improving the accuracy of PSI-BLAST protein database searches with composition-based statistics and other refinements&quot;, Nucleic Acids Res. 29:2994-3005.</BlastOutput_reference>
  <BlastOutput_db>/home/oohnohnoh1/Desktop/ACADEMIA/Papermaking/OPTIMUS_BIND/PANDAS_TABLE/db/cdd_delta</BlastOutput_db>
  <BlastOutput_query-ID>Query_1</BlastOutput_query-ID>
  <BlastOutput_query-def>A &lt;unknown description&gt;</BlastOutput_query-def>
  <BlastOutput_query-len>110</BlastOutput_query-len>
  <BlastOutput_param>
    <Parameters>
      <Parameters_matrix>BLOSUM62</Parameters_matrix>
      <Parameters_expect>0.0005</Parameters_expect>
      <Parameters_gap-open>11</Parameters_gap-open>
      <Parameters_gap-extend>1</Parameters_gap-extend>
      <Parameters_filter>F</Parameters_filter>
    </Parameters>
  </BlastOutput_param>
<BlastOutput_iterations>
<Iteration>
  <Iteration_iter-num>1</Iteration_iter-num>
  <Iteration_query-ID>Query_1</Iteration_query-ID>
  <Iteration_query-def>A &lt;unknown description&gt;</Iteration_query-def>
  <Iteration_query-len>110</Iteration_query-len>
<Iteration_hits>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>1</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|198178</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd09923, SH2_SOCS_family, Src homology 2 (SH2) domain found in  suppressor of cytokine signaling (SOCS) family.  SH2 domain found in SOCS proteins. SOCS was first recognized as a group of cytokine-inducible SH2 (CIS) domain proteins comprising eight family members in human (CIS and SOCS1-SOCS7). In addition to the SH2 domain, SOCS proteins have a variable N-terminal domain and a conserved SOCS box in the C-terminal domain. SOCS proteins bind to a substrate via their SH2 domain. The prototypical members, CIS and SOCS1-SOCS3, have been shown to regulate growth hormone signaling in vitro and in a classic negative feedback response compete for binding at phosphotyrosine sites in JAK kinase and receptor pathways to displace effector proteins and target bound receptors for proteasomal degradation. Loss of SOCS activity results in excessive cytokine signaling associated with a variety of hematopoietic, autoimmune, and inflammatory diseases and certain cancers. Members (SOCS4-SOCS7) were identified by their conserved SOCS box, an adapter motif of 3 helices that associates substrate binding domains, such as the SOCS SH2 domain, ankryin, and WD40 with ubiquitin ligase components. These show limited cytokine induction. In general SH2 domains are involved in signal transduction. They typically bind pTyr-containing ligands via two surface pockets, a pTyr and hydrophobic binding pocket, allowing proteins with SH2 domains to localize to tyrosine phosphorylated sites.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>198178</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>81</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>80.8777</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>198</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>7.41315e-22</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>22</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>105</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>1</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>81</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>40</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>53</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>3</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>84</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>GWYWGSMTVNEAKEKLKEAPEGTFLIRDSSHSDYLLTISVKTSAGPTNLRIEYQDGKFRLDSIICVKSKLKQFDSVVHLIDYYV</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>GWYWGGITRYEAEELLAGKPEGTFLVRDSSDSRYLFSVSFRTYGRTLHARIEYSNGRFSFDS---SDPSVPRFPCVVELIEHYV</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>GWYWG +T  EA+E L   PEGTFL+RDSS S YL ++S +T     + RIEY +G+F  DS       + +F  VV LI++YV</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>2</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|198251</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd10388, SH2_SOCS7, Src homology 2 (SH2) domain found in  suppressor of cytokine signaling (SOCS) proteins.  SH2 domain found in SOCS proteins. SOCS was first recognized as a group of cytokine-inducible SH2 (CIS) domain proteins comprising eight family members in human (CIS and SOCS1-SOCS7). In addition to the SH2 domain, SOCS proteins have a variable N-terminal domain and a conserved SOCS box in the C-terminal domain. SOCS proteins bind to a substrate via their SH2 domain. The prototypical members, CIS and SOCS1-SOCS3, have been shown to regulate growth hormone signaling in vitro and in a classic negative feedback response compete for binding at phosphotyrosine sites in JAK kinase and receptor pathways to displace effector proteins and target bound receptors for proteasomal degradation. Loss of SOCS activity results in excessive cytokine signaling associated with a variety of hematopoietic, autoimmune, and inflammatory diseases and certain cancers. Members (SOCS4-SOCS7) were identified by their conserved SOCS box, an adapter motif of 3 helices that associates substrate binding domains, such as the SOCS SH2 domain, ankryin, and WD40 with ubiquitin ligase components. These show limited cytokine induction. In general SH2 domains are involved in signal transduction. They typically bind pTyr-containing ligands via two surface pockets, a pTyr and hydrophobic binding pocket, allowing proteins with SH2 domains to localize to tyrosine phosphorylated sites.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>198251</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>101</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>64.6994</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>156</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>2.7898e-15</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>14</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>83</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>3</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>72</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>29</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>43</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>0</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>70</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>ALRELGQTGWYWGSMTVNEAKEKLKEAPEGTFLIRDSSHSDYLLTISVKTSAGPTNLRIEYQDGKFRLDS</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>SLRELKDCGWYWGPMSWEDAEKVLSNKPDGSFLVRDSSDDRYIFSLSFRSQGSVHHTRIEQYQGTFSLGS</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>+LREL   GWYWG M+  +A++ L   P+G+FL+RDSS   Y+ ++S ++     + RIE   G F L S</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>3</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|198195</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd09942, SH2_nSH2_p85_like, N-terminal Src homology 2 (nSH2) domain found in p85.  Phosphoinositide 3-kinases (PI3Ks) are essential for cell growth, migration, and survival. p110, the catalytic subunit, is composed of an adaptor-binding domain, a Ras-binding domain, a C2 domain, a helical domain, and a kinase domain.  The regulatory unit is called p85 and is composed of an SH3 domain, a RhoGap domain, a N-terminal SH2 (nSH2) domain, an internal SH2 (iSH2) domain, and C-terminal (cSH2) domain.  There are 2 inhibitory interactions between p110alpha and p85 of P13K: (1) p85 nSH2 domain with the C2, helical, and kinase domains of p110alpha and (2) p85 iSH2 domain with C2 domain of p110alpha. There are 3 inhibitory interactions between p110beta and p85 of P13K: (1) p85 nSH2 domain with the C2, helical, and kinase domains of p110beta, (2) p85 iSH2 domain with C2 domain of p110alpha, and (3) p85 cSH2 domain with the kinase domain of p110alpha. It is interesting to note that p110beta is oncogenic as a wild type protein while p110alpha lacks this ability. One explanation is the idea that the regulation of p110beta by p85 is unique because of the addition of inhibitory contacts from the cSH2 domain and the loss of contacts in the iSH2 domain. In general SH2 domains are involved in signal transduction. They typically bind pTyr-containing ligands via two surface pockets, a pTyr and hydrophobic binding pocket, allowing proteins with SH2 domains to localize to tyrosine phosphorylated sites.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>198195</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>110</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>61.6178</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>148</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>7.14327e-14</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>18</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>104</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>4</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>83</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>29</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>50</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>7</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>87</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>LGQTGWYWGSMTVNEAKEKLKEAPEGTFLIRDSSHSDYLLTISVKTSAGPTNLRIEYQDGKFRLDSIICVKSKLKQFDSVVHLIDYY</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>LQEAEWYWGDISREEVNEKMRDTPDGTFLVRDASTMKGDYTLTLRKGGNNKLIKIFHRDGKYGFSDPLT-------FNSVVELINYY</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>L +  WYWG ++  E  EK+++ P+GTFL+RD+S      T++++       ++I ++DGK+     +        F+SVV LI+YY</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>4</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|214585</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>smart00252, SH2, Src homology 2 domains.  Src homology 2 domains bind phosphotyrosine-containing polypeptides via 2 surface pockets. Specificity is provided via interaction with residues that are distinct from the phosphotyrosine. Only a single occurrence of a SH2 domain has been found in S. cerevisiae.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>214585</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>84</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>48.521</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>114</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>5.00517e-09</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>23</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>104</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>3</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>78</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>30</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>48</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>10</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>84</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>WYWGSMTVNEAKEKLKEAPEGTFLIRDSSHS--DYLLTISVKTSAGPTNLRIEYQDGKFRLDSIICVKSKLKQFDSVVHLIDYY</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>WYHGFISREEAEKLLKNEGDGDFLVRDSESSPGDYVLSVRVKGKVKHYRIR-RNEDGKFYLEGG-------RKFPSLVELVEHY</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>WY G ++  EA++ LK   +G FL+RDS  S  DY+L++ VK       +R   +DGKF L+         ++F S+V L+++Y</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>5</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|198193</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd09940, SH2_Vav_family, Src homology 2 (SH2) domain found in the Vav family.  Vav proteins are involved in several processes that require cytoskeletal reorganization, such as the formation of the immunological synapse (IS), phagocytosis, platelet aggregation, spreading, and transformation.  Vavs function as guanine nucleotide exchange factors (GEFs) for the Rho/Rac family of GTPases.  Vav family members have several conserved motifs/domains including: a leucine-rich region, a leucine-zipper, a calponin homology (CH) domain, an acidic domain, a Dbl-homology (DH) domain, a pleckstrin homology (PH) domain, a cysteine-rich domain, 2 SH3 domains,  a proline-rich region, and a SH2 domain.  Vavs are the only known Rho GEFs that have both the DH/PH motifs and SH2/SH3 domains in the same protein. The leucine-rich helix-loop-helix (HLH) domain is thought to be involved in protein heterodimerization with other HLH proteins and it may function as a negative regulator by forming inactive heterodimers. The CH domain  is usually involved in the association with filamentous actin, but in Vav it controls NFAT stimulation, Ca2+ mobilization, and its transforming activity. Acidic domains are involved in protein-protein interactions and contain regulatory tyrosines. The DH domain is a GDP-GTP exchange factor on Rho/Rac GTPases. The PH domain in involved in interactions with GTP-binding proteins, lipids and/or phosphorylated serine/threonine residues. The SH3 domain is involved in localization of proteins to specific sites within the cell interacting with protein with proline-rich sequences.  The SH2 domain mediates a high affinity interaction with tyrosine phosphorylated proteins.  There are three Vav mammalian family members: Vav1 which is expressed in the hematopoietic system, Vav2 and Vav3 are more ubiquitously expressed. The members here include insect and amphibian Vavs. In general SH2 domains are involved in signal transduction. They typically bind pTyr-containing ligands via two surface pockets, a pTyr and hydrophobic binding pocket, allowing proteins with SH2 domains to localize to tyrosine phosphorylated sites.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>198193</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>102</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>43.8986</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>102</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>3.40583e-07</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>17</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>104</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>1</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>82</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>25</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>49</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>8</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>89</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>ELGQTGWYWGSMTVNEAKEKLKEAPEGTFLIRDSSHSDYLLTISVKTSAGPTNLRIEYQ-DGKFRLDSIICVKSKLKQFDSVVHLIDYY</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>DLSEFLWFVGEMERDTAENRLENRPDGTYLVRVRPQGETQYALSIKYNGDVKHMKIEQRSDGLYYL-------SESRHFKSLVELVNYY</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>+L +  W+ G M  + A+ +L+  P+GT+L+R     +    +S+K +    +++IE + DG + L       S+ + F S+V L++YY</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>6</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|198190</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd09937, SH2_csk_like, Src homology 2 (SH2) domain found in Carboxyl-Terminal Src Kinase (Csk).  Both the C-terminal Src kinase (CSK) and CSK-homologous kinase (CHK) are members of the CSK-family of protein tyrosine kinases. These proteins suppress activity of Src-family kinases (SFK) by selectively phosphorylating the conserved C-terminal tail regulatory tyrosine by a similar mechanism. CHK is also capable of inhibiting SFKs by a non-catalytic mechanism that involves binding of CHK to SFKs to form stable protein complexes. The unphosphorylated form of SFKs is inhibited by CSK and CHK by a two-step mechanism. The first step involves the formation of a complex of SFKs with CSK/CHK with the SFKs in the complex are inactive. The second step, involves the phosphorylation of the C-terminal tail tyrosine of SFKs, which then dissociates and adopt an inactive conformation. The structural basis of how the phosphorylated SFKs dissociate from CSK/CHK to adopt the inactive conformation is not known. The inactive conformation of SFKs is stabilized by two intramolecular inhibitory interactions: (a) the pYT:SH2 interaction in which the phosphorylated C-terminal tail tyrosine (YT) binds to the SH2 domain, and (b) the linker:SH3 interaction of which the SH2-kinase domain linker binds to the SH3 domain. SFKs are activated by multiple mechanisms including binding of the ligands to the SH2 and SH3 domains to displace the two inhibitory intramolecular interactions, autophosphorylation, and dephosphorylation of YT. By selective phosphorylation and the non-catalytic inhibitory mechanism CSK and CHK are able to inhibit the active forms of SFKs. CSK and CHK are regulated by phosphorylation and inter-domain interactions. They both contain SH3, SH2, and kinase domains separated by the SH3-SH2 connector and SH2 kinase linker, intervening segments separating the three domains. They lack a conserved tyrosine phosphorylation site in the kinase domain and the C-terminal tail regulatory tyrosine phosphorylation site. The CSK SH2 domain is crucial for stabilizing the kinase domain in the active conformation. A disulfide bond here regulates CSK kinase activity. The subcellular localization and activity of CSK are regulated by its SH2 domain. In general SH2 domains are involved in signal transduction.  They typically bind pTyr-containing ligands via two surface pockets, a pTyr and hydrophobic binding pocket, allowing proteins with SH2 domains to localize to tyrosine phosphorylated sites.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>198190</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>98</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>41.2022</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>95</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>4.05773e-06</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>23</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>106</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>5</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>81</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>22</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>49</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>11</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>86</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>WYWGSMTVNEAKEKLKEAPEGTFLIRDSSH--SDYLLTISVKTSAGPTNLRIEYQDGKFRLDSIICVKSKLKQFDSVVHLIDYYVQ</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>WFHGKISREEAERLLQPPEDGLFLVRESTNYPGDYTLCVSFEGKV--EHYRVIYRNGKLTID-------EEEYFENLIQLVEHYTK</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>W+ G ++  EA+  L+   +G FL+R+S++   DY L +S +      + R+ Y++GK  +D       + + F++++ L+++Y +</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>7</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|198173</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd00173, SH2, Src homology 2 (SH2) domain.  In general, SH2 domains are involved in signal transduction; they bind pTyr-containing polypeptide ligands via two surface pockets, a pTyr and hydrophobic binding pocket, allowing proteins with SH2 domains to localize to tyrosine phosphorylated sites. They are present in a wide array of proteins including: adaptor proteins (Nck1, Crk, Grb2), scaffolds (Slp76, Shc, Dapp1), kinases (Src, Syk, Fps, Tec), phosphatases (Shp-1, Shp-2), transcription factors (STAT1),  Ras signaling molecules (Ras-Gap), ubiquitination factors (c-Cbl), cytoskeleton regulators (Tensin), signal regulators (SAP), and phospholipid second messengers (PLCgamma), amongst others.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>198173</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>79</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>38.5058</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>88</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>2.4432e-05</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>23</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>59</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>2</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>40</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>17</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>28</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>2</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>39</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>WYWGSMTVNEAKEKLKEAPEGTFLIRDSSH--SDYLLTI</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>WFHGSISREEAERLLRGKPDGTFLVRESSSEPGDYVLSV</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>W+ GS++  EA+  L+  P+GTFL+R+SS    DY+L++</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>8</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|198179</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd09925, SH2_SHC, Src homology 2 (SH2) domain found in SH2 adaptor protein C (SHC).  SHC is involved in a wide variety of pathways including regulating proliferation, angiogenesis, invasion and metastasis, and bone metabolism. An adapter protein, SHC has been implicated in Ras activation following the stimulation of a number of different receptors, including growth factors [insulin, epidermal growth factor (EGF), nerve growth factor, and platelet derived growth factor (PDGF)], cytokines [interleukins 2, 3, and 5], erythropoietin, and granulocyte/macrophage colony-stimulating factor, and antigens [T-cell and B-cell receptors]. SHC has been shown to bind to tyrosine-phosphorylated receptors, and receptor stimulation leads to tyrosine phosphorylation of SHC. Upon phosphorylation, SHC interacts with another adapter protein, Grb2, which binds to the Ras GTP/GDP exchange factor mSOS which leads to Ras activation. SHC is composed of an N-terminal domain that interacts with proteins containing phosphorylated tyrosines, a (glycine/proline)-rich collagen-homology domain that contains the phosphorylated binding site, and a C-terminal SH2 domain. SH2 has been shown to interact with the tyrosine-phosphorylated receptors of EGF and PDGF and with the tyrosine-phosphorylated C chain of the T-cell receptor, providing one of the mechanisms of T-cell-mediated Ras activation. In general SH2 domains are involved in signal transduction.  They typically bind pTyr-containing ligands via two surface pockets, a pTyr and hydrophobic binding pocket, allowing proteins with SH2 domains to localize to tyrosine phosphorylated sites.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>198179</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>104</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>38.891</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>89</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>3.06424e-05</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>23</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>105</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>9</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>81</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>23</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>45</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>10</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>83</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>WYWGSMTVNEAKEKLKEAPEGTFLIRDSSHSDYLLTISVKTSAGPTNLRIEYQDGKFRLDSIICVKSKLKQFDSVVHLIDYYV</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>WYHGKMSRRDAESLLQT--DGDFLVRESTTTPGQYVLTGMQNGQPKHLLLVDPEG--------VVRTKDRVFESISHLINYHV</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>WY G M+  +A+  L+   +G FL+R+S+ +     ++   +  P +L +   +G         V++K + F+S+ HLI+Y+V</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>9</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|333769</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>pfam00017, SH2, SH2 domain.  </Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>333769</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>76</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>36.965</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>84</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>9.62114e-05</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>23</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>104</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>1</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>76</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>22</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>42</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>8</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>83</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>WYWGSMTVNEAKEKLKEA-PEGTFLIRDSSHSDYLLTISVKTSAGPTNLRIEYQDGKFRLDSIICVKSKLKQFDSVVHLIDYY</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>WYHGKISRQEAERLLLNGKPDGTFLVRESESTPGDYTLSVRDDGKVKHYKIQSTDNGYYISGGV-------KFSSLAELVEHY</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>WY G ++  EA+  L    P+GTFL+R+S  +    T+SV+      + +I+  D  + +   +       +F S+  L+++Y</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>10</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|198186</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd09932, SH2_C-SH2_PLC_gamma_like, C-terminal Src homology 2 (C-SH2) domain in Phospholipase C gamma.  Phospholipase C gamma is a signaling molecule that is recruited to the C-terminal tail of the receptor upon autophosphorylation of a highly conserved tyrosine. PLCgamma is composed of a Pleckstrin homology (PH) domain followed by an elongation factor (EF) domain, 2 catalytic regions of PLC domains that flank 2 tandem SH2 domains (N-SH2, C-SH2), and ending with a SH3 domain and C2 domain. N-SH2 SH2 domain-mediated interactions represent a crucial step in transmembrane signaling by receptor tyrosine kinases. SH2 domains recognize phosphotyrosine (pY) in the context of particular sequence motifs in receptor phosphorylation sites. Both N-SH2 and C-SH2 have a very similar binding affinity to pY. But in growth factor stimulated cells these domains bind to different target proteins. N-SH2 binds to pY containing sites in the C-terminal tails of tyrosine kinases and other receptors. Recently it has been shown that this interaction is mediated by phosphorylation-independent interactions between a secondary binding site found exclusively on the N-SH2 domain and a region of the FGFR1 tyrosine kinase domain. This secondary site on the SH2 cooperates with the canonical pY site to regulate selectivity in mediating a specific cellular process.  C-SH2 binds to an intramolecular site on PLCgamma itself which allows it to hydrolyze phosphatidylinositol-4,5-bisphosphate into diacylglycerol and inositol triphosphate. These then activate protein kinase C and release calcium. In general SH2 domains are involved in signal transduction. They typically bind pTyr-containing ligands via two surface pockets, a pTyr and hydrophobic binding pocket, allowing proteins with SH2 domains to localize to tyrosine phosphorylated sites.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>198186</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>104</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>37.3502</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>85</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>0.00010985</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>23</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>104</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>6</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>80</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>23</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>39</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>9</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>83</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>WYWGSMTVNEAKEKLKEAP-EGTFLIRDSSHSDYLLTISVKTSAGPTNLRIEYQDGKFRLDSIICVKSKLKQFDSVVHLIDYY</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>WFHANLTREQAEEMLMRVPRDGAFLVRPSETDPNSFAISFRAEGKIKHCRIKQEGRLFVIGT--------SQFESLVELVSYY</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>W+  ++T  +A+E L   P +G FL+R S        IS +      + RI+ +   F + +         QF+S+V L+ YY</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
</Iteration_hits>
  <Iteration_stat>
    <Statistics>
      <Statistics_db-num>29480</Statistics_db-num>
      <Statistics_db-len>6494941</Statistics_db-len>
      <Statistics_hsp-len>73</Statistics_hsp-len>
      <Statistics_eff-space>160687337</Statistics_eff-space>
      <Statistics_kappa>0.041</Statistics_kappa>
      <Statistics_lambda>0.267</Statistics_lambda>
      <Statistics_entropy>0.14</Statistics_entropy>
    </Statistics>
  </Iteration_stat>
</Iteration>
</BlastOutput_iterations>
</BlastOutput>

