<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE BlastOutput PUBLIC "-//NCBI//NCBI BlastOutput/EN" "http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/dtd/NCBI_BlastOutput.dtd">
<BlastOutput>
  <BlastOutput_program>psiblast</BlastOutput_program>
  <BlastOutput_version>PSIBLAST 2.9.0+</BlastOutput_version>
  <BlastOutput_reference>Alejandro A. Sch&amp;auml;ffer, L. Aravind, Thomas L. Madden, Sergei Shavirin, John L. Spouge, Yuri I. Wolf, Eugene V. Koonin, and Stephen F. Altschul (2001), &quot;Improving the accuracy of PSI-BLAST protein database searches with composition-based statistics and other refinements&quot;, Nucleic Acids Res. 29:2994-3005.</BlastOutput_reference>
  <BlastOutput_db>/home/oohnohnoh1/Desktop/ACADEMIA/Papermaking/OPTIMUS_BIND/PANDAS_TABLE/db/cdd_delta</BlastOutput_db>
  <BlastOutput_query-ID>Query_1</BlastOutput_query-ID>
  <BlastOutput_query-def>A &lt;unknown description&gt;</BlastOutput_query-def>
  <BlastOutput_query-len>87</BlastOutput_query-len>
  <BlastOutput_param>
    <Parameters>
      <Parameters_matrix>BLOSUM62</Parameters_matrix>
      <Parameters_expect>0.0005</Parameters_expect>
      <Parameters_gap-open>11</Parameters_gap-open>
      <Parameters_gap-extend>1</Parameters_gap-extend>
      <Parameters_filter>F</Parameters_filter>
    </Parameters>
  </BlastOutput_param>
<BlastOutput_iterations>
<Iteration>
  <Iteration_iter-num>1</Iteration_iter-num>
  <Iteration_query-ID>Query_1</Iteration_query-ID>
  <Iteration_query-def>A &lt;unknown description&gt;</Iteration_query-def>
  <Iteration_query-len>87</Iteration_query-len>
<Iteration_hits>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>1</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|340449</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd00153, RA_RalGDS_like, Ras-associating (RA) domain of RalGDS family.  The RalGDS family RA domains can interact with activated Ras and may function as effectors for other Ras family. Ras proteins are small GTPases that are involved in cellular signal transduction. The RA domain has the beta-grasp ubiquitin-like (Ubl) fold with low sequence similarity to ubiquitin (Ub); Ub is a protein modifier in eukaryotes and is involved in various cellular processes, including transcriptional regulation, cell cycle control, and DNA repair. The RalGDS family includes RalGDS, RGL, RGL2/Rlf and RGL3. All family members have similar domain structure: a central CDC25 homology domain with an upstream Ras Exchange motif (REM), and a C-terminal RA domain. The RA domain mediates the GTP-dependent interaction with Ras and Ras-related proteins.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>340449</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>88</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>112.849</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>281</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>1.19169e-34</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>2</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>87</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>1</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>88</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>51</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>77</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>2</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>88</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>DCCIIRVSLD--VDNGNMYKSILVTSQDKAPTVIRKAMDKHNLDEDEPEDYELLQIISEDHKLKIPENANVFYAMNSAANYDFILKKR</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>DSRIIRVSLEDGSEDGNLYKSILLTNQDRTPSVIRRALEKHNLEDEDPDDFSLVQILPDDKELVIPDNANVFYAMNSSANLNFILRKK</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>D  IIRVSL+   ++GN+YKSIL+T+QD+ P+VIR+A++KHNL++++P+D+ L+QI+ +D +L IP+NANVFYAMNS+AN +FIL+K+</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>2</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|214612</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>smart00314, RA, Ras association (RalGDS/AF-6) domain.  RasGTP effectors (in cases of AF6, canoe and RalGDS); putative RasGTP effectors in other cases. Kalhammer et al. have shown that not all RA domains bind RasGTP. Predicted structure similar to that determined, and that of the RasGTP-binding domain of Raf kinase. Predicted RA domains in PLC210 and nore1 found to bind RasGTP. Included outliers (Grb7, Grb14, adenylyl cyclases etc.).</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>214612</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>90</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>46.595</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>109</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>1.17699e-08</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>2</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>87</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>1</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>89</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>26</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>51</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>5</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>90</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>DCCIIRVSLDVDNGNMYKSILVTSQDKAPTVIRKAMDKHNLDEDEPEDYELLQIISEDHKLKIPENANVFYAM----NSAANYDFILKKR</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>DTFVLRVYVDDLPGGTYKTLRVSSRTTARDVIQQLLEKFHL-TDDPEEYVLVEVLPDGKERVLPDDENPLQLQKLWPRRGPNLRFVLRKR</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>D  ++RV +D   G  YK++ V+S+  A  VI++ ++K +L  D+PE+Y L++++ +  +  +P++ N             N  F+L+KR</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>3</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|307093</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>pfam00788, RA, Ras association (RalGDS/AF-6) domain.  RasGTP effectors (in cases of AF6, canoe and RalGDS); putative RasGTP effectors in other cases. Recent evidence (not yet in MEDLINE) shows that some RA domains do NOT bind RasGTP. Predicted structure similar to that determined, and that of the RasGTP-binding domain of Raf kinase.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>307093</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>93</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>41.9726</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>97</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>8.23712e-07</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>15</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>87</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>15</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>91</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>26</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>43</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>6</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>78</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>GNMYKSILVTSQDKAPTVIRKAMDKHNLDEDEPEDYELLQIISE-DHKLKIPENANVFYAM----NSAANYDFILKKR</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>GTTYKSILVSSSTTAEEVIRALLEKFGL-EDDPRDYVLVEVLERGGGERRLPDDECPLQIQLQWPRDASDSRFLLRKR</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>G  YKSILV+S   A  VIR  ++K  L ED+P DY L++++     + ++P++             A++  F+L+KR</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>4</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|340563</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd17043, RA, Ras-associating (RA) domain, structurally similar to a beta-grasp ubiquitin-like fold.  RA domain-containing proteins function by interacting with Ras proteins directly or indirectly and are involved in various functions ranging from tumor suppression to being oncoproteins. Ras proteins are small GTPases that are involved in cellular signal transduction. The RA domain has the beta-grasp ubiquitin-like (Ubl) fold with low sequence similarity to ubiquitin (Ub); Ub is a protein modifier in eukaryotes that is involved in various cellular processes, including transcriptional regulation, cell cycle control, and DNA repair. RA-containing proteins include RalGDS, AF6, RIN, RASSF1, SNX27, CYR1, STE50, and phospholipase C epsilon.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>340563</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>87</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>40.4318</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>93</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>2.92698e-06</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>11</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>55</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>8</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>51</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>20</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>31</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>1</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>45</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>DVDNGNMYKSILVTSQDKAPTVIRKAMDKHNLDEDEPEDYELLQI</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>DLAPGSAYKSILVSSTTTAREVVQLLLEKYGLEED-PEDYSLYEV</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>D+  G+ YKSILV+S   A  V++  ++K+ L+ED PEDY L ++</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>5</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|340479</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd01781, RA2_Afadin, Ras-associating (RA) domain 2 found in Afadin.  Afadin, also termed ALL1-fused gene from chromosome 6 protein (AF-6), or canoe, is involved in many fundamental signaling cascades in cells. In addition, it is involved in oncogenesis and metastasis. Afadin has multiple domains: from the N-terminus to the C-terminus it has two Ras-associated (RA) domains, a forkhead-associated domain, a dilute domain, a PDZ domain, three proline-rich domains, and an F-actin binding domain. RA domain-containing proteins function by interacting with Ras proteins directly or indirectly and are involved in several different functions ranging from tumor suppression to being oncoproteins. Ras proteins are small GTPases that are involved in cellular signal transduction. The RA domain has a beta-grasp ubiquitin-like (Ubl) fold with low sequence similarity to ubiquitin (Ub). Ub is a protein modifier in eukaryotes that is involved in various cellular processes including transcriptional regulation, cell cycle control, and DNA repair in eukaryotes. Afadin is abundant at cadherin-based adherens junctions in epithelial cells, endothelial cells, and fibroblasts. This family corresponds to the second RA domain of afadin.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>340479</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>102</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>40.817</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>94</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>3.12067e-06</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>18</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>56</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>17</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>55</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>15</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>32</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>0</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>39</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>YKSILVTSQDKAPTVIRKAMDKHNLDEDEPEDYELLQII</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>YKTLLLSTNDTADFVVREALEKYGLEKENPKDYCLVQVV</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>YK++L+++ D A  V+R+A++K+ L+++ P+DY L+Q++</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>6</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|340481</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd01783, RA2_DAGK-theta, Ras-associating (RA) domain 2 found in diacylgylcerol kinase theta (DAGK-theta) and similar proteins.  DAGK phosphorylates the second messenger diacylglycerol to phosphatidic acid as part of a protein kinase C pathway. DAGK-theta is characterized as a type V DAGK that has three cysteine-rich domains (all other isoforms have two), a proline/glycine-rich domain at its N-terminal, and a proposed Ras-associating (RA) domain. RA domain-containing proteins function by interacting with Ras proteins directly or indirectly and are involved in several different functions ranging from tumor suppression to being oncoproteins. Ras proteins are small GTPases that are involved in cellular signal transduction. The RA domain has a beta-grasp ubiquitin-like (Ubl) fold with low sequence similarity to ubiquitin (Ub). Ub is a protein modifier in eukaryotes that is involved in various cellular processes including transcriptional regulation, cell cycle control, and DNA repair in eukaryotes. There are ten mammalian isoforms of DAGK have been identified to date, these are organized into five categories based on the domain architecture. DAGK-theta also contains a pleckstrin homology (PH) domain. The subcellular localization and the activity of DAGK-theta are regulated in a complex (stimulation- and cell type-dependent) manner. This family corresponds to the second RA domain of DAGK-theta.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>340481</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>95</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>37.3502</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>85</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>5.00875e-05</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>15</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>56</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>13</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>54</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>16</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>28</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>0</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>42</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>GNMYKSILVTSQDKAPTVIRKAMDKHNLDEDEPEDYELLQII</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>GVAYKSIPVTKETTVEEVIKEALPKFGLQDEDPEDFRLVEVL</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>G  YKSI VT +     VI++A+ K  L +++PED+ L++++</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
</Iteration_hits>
  <Iteration_stat>
    <Statistics>
      <Statistics_db-num>29480</Statistics_db-num>
      <Statistics_db-len>6494941</Statistics_db-len>
      <Statistics_hsp-len>54</Statistics_hsp-len>
      <Statistics_eff-space>161799693</Statistics_eff-space>
      <Statistics_kappa>0.041</Statistics_kappa>
      <Statistics_lambda>0.267</Statistics_lambda>
      <Statistics_entropy>0.14</Statistics_entropy>
    </Statistics>
  </Iteration_stat>
</Iteration>
</BlastOutput_iterations>
</BlastOutput>

