<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE BlastOutput PUBLIC "-//NCBI//NCBI BlastOutput/EN" "http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/dtd/NCBI_BlastOutput.dtd">
<BlastOutput>
  <BlastOutput_program>psiblast</BlastOutput_program>
  <BlastOutput_version>PSIBLAST 2.9.0+</BlastOutput_version>
  <BlastOutput_reference>Alejandro A. Sch&amp;auml;ffer, L. Aravind, Thomas L. Madden, Sergei Shavirin, John L. Spouge, Yuri I. Wolf, Eugene V. Koonin, and Stephen F. Altschul (2001), &quot;Improving the accuracy of PSI-BLAST protein database searches with composition-based statistics and other refinements&quot;, Nucleic Acids Res. 29:2994-3005.</BlastOutput_reference>
  <BlastOutput_db>/home/oohnohnoh1/Desktop/ACADEMIA/Papermaking/OPTIMUS_BIND/PANDAS_TABLE/db/cdd_delta</BlastOutput_db>
  <BlastOutput_query-ID>Query_1</BlastOutput_query-ID>
  <BlastOutput_query-def>B &lt;unknown description&gt;</BlastOutput_query-def>
  <BlastOutput_query-len>460</BlastOutput_query-len>
  <BlastOutput_param>
    <Parameters>
      <Parameters_matrix>BLOSUM62</Parameters_matrix>
      <Parameters_expect>0.0005</Parameters_expect>
      <Parameters_gap-open>11</Parameters_gap-open>
      <Parameters_gap-extend>1</Parameters_gap-extend>
      <Parameters_filter>F</Parameters_filter>
    </Parameters>
  </BlastOutput_param>
<BlastOutput_iterations>
<Iteration>
  <Iteration_iter-num>1</Iteration_iter-num>
  <Iteration_query-ID>Query_1</Iteration_query-ID>
  <Iteration_query-def>B &lt;unknown description&gt;</Iteration_query-def>
  <Iteration_query-len>460</Iteration_query-len>
<Iteration_hits>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>1</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|176533</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd08591, PI-PLCc_beta, Catalytic domain of metazoan phosphoinositide-specific phospholipase C-beta.  This subfamily corresponds to the catalytic domain present in metazoan phosphoinositide-specific phospholipase C (PI-PLC, EC 3.1.4.11)-beta isozymes. PI-PLC is a signaling enzyme that hydrolyzes the membrane phospholipids phosphatidylinositol-4,5-bisphosphate (PIP2)  to generate two important second messengers in eukaryotic signal transduction cascades,  Inositol 1,4,5-trisphosphate (InsP3) and diacylglycerol (DAG). InsP3 triggers inflow of calcium from intracellular stores, while DAG, together with calcium, activates protein kinase C, which goes on to phosphorylate other molecules, leading to altered cellular activity. Calcium is required for the catalysis. PLC-beta represents a class of mammalian PI-PLC that has an N-terminal pleckstrin homology (PH) domain, an array of EF hands, a PLC catalytic core domain, a C2 domain, and a unique C-terminal coiled-coil (CT) domain necessary for homodimerization. The PLC catalytic core domain is a TIM barrel with two highly conserved regions (X and Y) split by a highly degenerate linker sequence. There are four PLC-beta isozymes (1-4). They are activated by the heterotrimeric G protein alpha q subunits through their C2 domain and long C-terminal extension. The beta-gamma subunits of heterotrimeric G proteins are known to activate the PLC-beta2 and -beta3 isozymes only. Aside from four PLC-beta isozymes identified in mammals, some eukaryotic PLC-beta homologs have been classified into this subfamily, such as NorpA and PLC-21 from Drosophila and PLC-beta from turkey, Xenopus, sponge, and hydra.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>176533</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>257</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>240.35</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>612</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>4.34642e-77</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>308</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>459</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>3</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>153</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>114</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>124</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>1</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>152</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>DMTQPLSAYFINSSHNTYLTAGQLAGTSSVEMYRQALLWGCRCVELDVWKGRPPEEEPFITHGFTMTTEVPLRDVLEAIAETAFKTSPYPVILSFENHVDSAKQQAKMAEYCRSIFGDALLIEPLDKYPLAPGVPLPSPQDLMGRILVKNKK</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>DMDQPLSHYFINSSHNTYLTGRQFGGKSSVEMYRQVLLSGCRCIELDCWDGKGEDEEPIITHGKTMCTEILFKDVIEAIAETAFKTSEYPVILSFENHC-SSKQQAKMAEYCREIFGDLLLTEPLEKYPLEPGVPLPSPNDLKRKILIKNKK</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>DM QPLS YFINSSHNTYLT  Q  G SSVEMYRQ LL GCRC+ELD W G+  +EEP ITHG TM TE+  +DV+EAIAETAFKTS YPVILSFENH  S+KQQAKMAEYCR IFGD LL EPL+KYPL PGVPLPSP DL  +IL+KNKK</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>2</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|176535</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd08593, PI-PLCc_delta, Catalytic domain of metazoan phosphoinositide-specific phospholipase C-delta.  This subfamily corresponds to the catalytic domain present in metazoan phosphoinositide-specific phospholipase C (PI-PLC, EC 3.1.4.11)-delta isozymes. PI-PLC is a signaling enzyme that hydrolyzes the membrane phospholipids phosphatidylinositol-4,5-bisphosphate (PIP2)  to generate two important second messengers in eukaryotic signal transduction cascades,  Inositol 1,4,5-trisphosphate (InsP3) and diacylglycerol (DAG). InsP3 triggers inflow of calcium from intracellular stores, while DAG, together with calcium, activates protein kinase C, which then phosphorylates other molecules, leading to altered cellular activity. Calcium is required for the catalysis. PLC-delta represents a class of mammalian PI-PLC that has an N-terminal pleckstrin homology (PH) domain, an array of EF hands, a PLC catalytic core domain, and a C-terminal C2 domain. This CD corresponds to the catalytic domain which is a TIM barrel with two highly conserved regions (X and Y) split by a highly degenerate linker sequence. There are three PI-PLC-delta isozymes (1,3 and 4). PI-PLC-delta1 is relatively well characterized. It is activated by high calcium levels generated by other PI-PLC family members, and therefore functions as a calcium amplifier within the cell. Different PI-PLC-delta isozymes have different tissue distribution and different subcellular locations. PI-PLC-delta1 is mostly a cytoplasmic protein, PI-PLC-delta3 is located in the membrane, and PI-PLC-delta4 is predominantly detected in the cell nucleus. Aside from three PI-PLC-delta isozymes identified in mammals, some eukaryotic PI-PLC-delta homologs have been classified to this CD.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>176535</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>257</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>174.096</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>440</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>1.53342e-51</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>308</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>459</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>3</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>147</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>90</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>107</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>7</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>152</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>DMTQPLSAYFINSSHNTYLTAGQLAGTSSVEMYRQALLWGCRCVELDVWKGRPPEEEPFITHGFTMTTEVPLRDVLEAIAETAFKTSPYPVILSFENHVDSAKQQAKMAEYCRSIFGDALLIEPLDKYPLAPGVPLPSPQDLMGRILVKNKK</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>DMTQPLSHYFIASSHNTYLLEDQLKGPSSTEAYIRALKKGCRCVELDCWDG--PDGEPIIYHGHTLTSKILFKDVIQAIREYAFKVSPYPVILSLENHC-SVEQQKVMAQHLKSILGDKLLTQPLDGVLTA----LPSPEELKGKILVKGKK</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>DMTQPLS YFI SSHNTYL   QL G SS E Y +AL  GCRCVELD W G  P+ EP I HG T+T+++  +DV++AI E AFK SPYPVILS ENH  S +QQ  MA++ +SI GD LL +PLD    A    LPSP++L G+ILVK KK</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>3</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|334053</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>pfam00388, PI-PLC-X, Phosphatidylinositol-specific phospholipase C, X domain.  This associates with pfam00387 to form a single structural unit.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>334053</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>145</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>169.088</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>427</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>3.961e-51</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>309</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>448</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>1</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>134</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>88</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>100</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>6</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>140</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>MTQPLSAYFINSSHNTYLTAGQLAGTSSVEMYRQALLWGCRCVELDVWKGRPPEEEPFITHGFTMTTEVPLRDVLEAIAETAFKTSPYPVILSFENHVDSAKQQAKMAEYCRSIFGDALLIEPLDKYPLAPGVPLPSPQD</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>MSQPLSHYFISSSHNTYLTGDQLTGKSSVEAYIRALLRGCRCVELDCWDG--PDGEPVVYHGYTLTSPIPFRDVLEAIKEYAFVTSPYPVILSLENHC-SPEQQKKMAEILKEIFGDMLYTPPLDDEDLT---ELPSPED</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>M+QPLS YFI+SSHNTYLT  QL G SSVE Y +ALL GCRCVELD W G  P+ EP + HG+T+T+ +P RDVLEAI E AF TSPYPVILS ENH  S +QQ KMAE  + IFGD L   PLD   L     LPSP+D</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>4</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|320030</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd16200, EFh_PI-PLCbeta, EF-hand motif found in metazoan phosphoinositide-specific phospholipase C (PI-PLC)-beta isozymes.  PI-PLC-beta isozymes represent a class of metazoan PI-PLCs that hydrolyze the membrane lipid phosphatidylinositol 4,5-bisphosphate (PIP2) to propagate diverse intracellular responses that underlie the physiological action of many hormones, neurotransmitters, and growth factors (EC 3.1.4.11). They have been implicated in numerous processes relevant to central nervous system (CNS), including chemotaxis, cardiovascular function, neuronal signaling, and opioid sensitivity. Like other PI-PLC isozymes, PI-PLC-beta isozymes contain a core set of domains, including an N-terminal pleckstrin homology (PH) domain, four atypical EF-hand motifs, a PLC catalytic core, and a single C2 domain. Besides, they have a unique C-terminal coiled-coil (CT) domain necessary for homodimerization. The PLC catalytic core domain is a TIM barrel with two highly conserved regions (X and Y) split by a highly degenerate linker sequence. There are four PI-PLC-beta isozymes (1-4). PI-PLC-beta1 and PI-PLC-beta3 are expressed in a wide range of tissues and cell types, whereas PI-PLC-beta2 and PI-PLC-beta4 have been found only in hematopoietic and neuronal tissues, respectively. All PI-PLC-beta isozymes are activated by the heterotrimeric G protein alpha subunits of the Gq class through their C2 domain and long C-terminal extension. They are GTPase-activating proteins (GAPs) for these G alpha(q) proteins. PI-PLC-beta2 and PI-PLC-beta3 can also be activated by beta-gamma subunits of the G alpha(i/o) family of heterotrimeric G proteins and the small GTPases such as Rac and Cdc42. This family also includes two invertebrate homologs of PI-PLC-beta, PLC21 from cephalopod retina and No receptor potential A protein (NorpA) from Drosophila melanogaster.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>320030</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>153</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>167.933</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>424</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>1.45678e-50</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>144</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>294</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>1</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>153</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>85</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>116</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>2</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>153</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>RKAYTKLKLQVNQDGRIPVKNILKMFSADKKR--VETALESCGLKFNRSESIRPDEFSLEIFERFLNKLCLRPDIDKILLEIGAKGKPYLTLEQLMDFINQKQRDPRLNEVLYPPLRPSQARLLIEKYEPNQQFLERDQMSMEGFSRYLGGEE</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>KKLYTKLKLSVNITGKIPVKNIIKCFSSDKKRKRVLKALKALGLPDGKNDEIDPEDFTFEKFFKLYNKLCPRPDIDEIFKELGGKRKPYLTLEQLVDFLNEEQRDPRLNEILFPFHTKEQAKKLIDKYEPNEKNKKKGQLTLEGFLRYLMSDE</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>+K YTKLKL VN  G+IPVKNI+K FS+DKKR  V  AL++ GL   +++ I P++F+ E F +  NKLC RPDID+I  E+G K KPYLTLEQL+DF+N++QRDPRLNE+L+P     QA+ LI+KYEPN++  ++ Q+++EGF RYL  +E</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>5</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|176501</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd08558, PI-PLCc_eukaryota, Catalytic domain of eukaryotic phosphoinositide-specific phospholipase C and similar proteins.  This family corresponds to the catalytic domain present in eukaryotic phosphoinositide-specific phospholipase C (PI-PLC, EC 3.1.4.11) and similar proteins. The higher eukaryotic PI-PLCs play a critical role in most signal transduction pathways, controlling numerous cellular events such as cell growth, proliferation, excitation and secretion. They strictly require Ca2+ for the catalytic activity. They display a clear preference towards the hydrolysis of the more highly phosphorylated membrane phospholipids PI-analogues, phosphatidylinositol 4,5-bisphosphate (PIP2) and phosphatidylinositol-4-phosphate (PIP), to generate two important second messengers in eukaryotic signal transduction cascades, inositol 1,4,5-trisphosphate (InsP3) and diacylglycerol (DAG). InsP3 triggers inflow of calcium from intracellular stores, while DAG, together with calcium, activates protein kinase C, which then phosphorylates other molecules, leading to altered cellular activity. The eukaryotic PI-PLCs have a multidomain organization that consists of a PLC catalytic core domain, and various regulatory domains, such as the pleckstrin homology (PH) domain, EF-hand motif, and C2 domain. The catalytic core domain is a TIM barrel with two highly conserved regions (X and Y) split by a linker region. The catalytic mechanism of eukaryotic PI-PLCs is based on general base and acid catalysis utilizing two well conserved histidines and consists of two steps, a phosphotransfer and a phosphodiesterase reaction. The mammalian PI-PLCs consist of 13 isozymes, which are classified into six-subfamilies, PI-PLC-delta (1,3 and 4), -beta(1-4), -gamma(1,2), -epsilon, -zeta, and -eta (1,2). Ca2+ is required for the activation of all forms of mammalian PI-PLCs, and the concentration of calcium influences substrate specificity. This family also includes metazoan phospholipase C related but catalytically inactive proteins (PRIP), which belong to a group of novel inositol trisphosphate binding proteins. Due to the replacement of critical catalytic residues, PRIP does not have PLC enzymatic activity.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>176501</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>226</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>169.088</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>427</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>4.80352e-50</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>308</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>447</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>3</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>135</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>87</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>102</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>7</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>140</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>DMTQPLSAYFINSSHNTYLTAGQLAGTSSVEMYRQALLWGCRCVELDVWKGRPPEEEPFITHGFTMTTEVPLRDVLEAIAETAFKTSPYPVILSFENHVDSAKQQAKMAEYCRSIFGDALLIEPLDKYPLAPGVPLPSPQ</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>DMTQPLSHYFISSSHNTYLTGDQLTGESSVEAYIRALLRGCRCVELDCWDG--PDGEPVVYHGHTLTSKILFKDVIEAIKEYAFVTSPYPVILSLENHC-SLEQQKKMAQILKEIFGDKLLTPPLDENP----VQLPSPE</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>DMTQPLS YFI+SSHNTYLT  QL G SSVE Y +ALL GCRCVELD W G  P+ EP + HG T+T+++  +DV+EAI E AF TSPYPVILS ENH  S +QQ KMA+  + IFGD LL  PLD+ P    V LPSP+</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>6</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|320043</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd16213, EFh_PI-PLC21, EF-hand motif found in phosphoinositide phospholipase PLC21 and similar proteins.  The family includes invertebrate homologs of phosphoinositide phospholipase C beta (PI-PLC-beta) named PLC21 from cephalopod retina. It also includes PLC21 encoded by plc-21 gene, which is expressed in the central nervous system of Drosophila. Like beta-class of vertebrate PI-PLCs, PLC21 contains an N-terminal pleckstrin homology (PH) domain, four atypical EF-hand motifs, a PLC catalytic core, and a single C2 domain. The PLC catalytic core domain is a TIM barrel with two highly conserved regions (X and Y) split by a highly degenerate linker sequence.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>320043</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>154</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>165.236</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>417</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>1.61238e-49</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>145</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>294</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>2</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>154</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>81</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>112</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>3</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>153</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>KAYTKLKLQVNQDGRIPVKNILKMFSA---DKKRVETALESCGLKFNRSESIRPDEFSLEIFERFLNKLCLRPDIDKILLEIGAKGKPYLTLEQLMDFINQKQRDPRLNEVLYPPLRPSQARLLIEKYEPNQQFLERDQMSMEGFSRYLGGEE</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>KAYTKLTLQTDKEGKIPVKNIVKMFAQHKDDRKRVEKALEAIGLPSGKNDAIDPKKFTFEDFFNFYRRLTGRQEVEKIFDELGAKKKPYLTTEQFVDFLNKTQRDPRLNEILYPYANPKRARDLINQYEPNKSFAKKGHLSVEGFLRYLMSED</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>KAYTKL LQ +++G+IPVKNI+KMF+    D+KRVE ALE+ GL   ++++I P +F+ E F  F  +L  R +++KI  E+GAK KPYLT EQ +DF+N+ QRDPRLNE+LYP   P +AR LI +YEPN+ F ++  +S+EGF RYL  E+</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>7</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|176540</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd08598, PI-PLC1c_yeast, Catalytic domain of putative yeast phosphatidylinositide-specific phospholipases C.  This family corresponds to the catalytic domain present in a group of putative phosphoinositide-specific phospholipase C (PI-PLC, EC 3.1.4.11) encoded by PLC1 genes from yeasts, which are homologs of the delta isoforms of mammalian PI-PLC in terms of overall sequence similarity and domain organization. Mammalian PI-PLC is a signaling enzyme that hydrolyzes the membrane phospholipids phosphatidylinositol-4,5-bisphosphate (PIP2)  to generate two important second messengers in eukaryotic signal transduction cascades,  inositol 1,4,5-trisphosphate (InsP3) and diacylglycerol (DAG). InsP3 triggers inflow of calcium from intracellular stores, while DAG, together with calcium, activates protein kinase C, which then phosphorylates other molecules, leading to altered cellular activity. Calcium is required for the catalysis. The prototype of this CD is protein Plc1p encoded by PLC1 genes from Saccharomyces cerevisiae. Plc1p contains both highly conserved X- and Y- regions of PLC catalytic core domain, as well as a presumptive EF-hand like calcium binding motif.  Experiments show that Plc1p displays calcium dependent catalytic properties with high similarity to those of the mammalian PLCs, and plays multiple roles in modulating the membrane/protein interactions in filamentation control. CaPlc1p encoded by CAPLC1 from the closely related yeast Candida albicans, an orthologue of S. cerevisiae Plc1p, is also included in this group. Like Plc1p, CaPlc1p has conserved presumptive catalytic domain, shows PLC activity when expressed in E. coli, and is involved in multiple cellular processes. There are two other gene copies of CAPLC1 in C. albicans, CAPLC2 (also named as PIPLC) and CAPLC3. Experiments show CaPlc1p is the only enzyme in C. albicans which functions as PLC. The biological functions of CAPLC2 and CAPLC3 gene products must be clearly different from CaPlc1p, but their exact roles remain unclear. Moreover, CAPLC2 and CAPLC3 gene products are more similar to extracellular bacterial PI-PLC than to the eukaryotic PI-PLC, and they are not included in this subfamily.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>176540</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>231</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>166.007</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>419</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>1.00149e-48</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>308</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>459</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>3</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>147</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>85</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>107</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>7</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>152</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>DMTQPLSAYFINSSHNTYLTAGQLAGTSSVEMYRQALLWGCRCVELDVWKGRPPEEEPFITHGFTMTTEVPLRDVLEAIAETAFKTSPYPVILSFENHVDSAKQQAKMAEYCRSIFGDALLIEPLDKYPLAPGVPLPSPQDLMGRILVKNKK</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>DLSRPLNEYFISSSHNTYLLGRQLAGDSSVEGYIRALQRGCRCVEIDVWDG--DDGEPVVTHGYTLTSSVPFRDVCRAIKKYAFVTSPYPLILSLEVHCD-AEQQERMVEIMKETFGDLLVTEPLDGLE----DELPSPEELRGKILIKVKK</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>D+++PL+ YFI+SSHNTYL   QLAG SSVE Y +AL  GCRCVE+DVW G   + EP +THG+T+T+ VP RDV  AI + AF TSPYP+ILS E H D A+QQ +M E  +  FGD L+ EPLD         LPSP++L G+IL+K KK</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>8</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|197543</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>smart00148, PLCXc, Phospholipase C, catalytic domain (part); domain X.  Phosphoinositide-specific phospholipases C. These enzymes contain 2 regions (X and Y) which together form a TIM barrel-like structure containing the active site residues. Phospholipase C enzymes (PI-PLC) act as signal transducers that generate two second messengers, inositol-1,4,5-trisphosphate and diacylglycerol. The bacterial enzyme appears to be a homologue of the mammalian PLCs.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>197543</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>143</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>153.68</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>387</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>2.5712e-45</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>309</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>456</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>1</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>141</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>87</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>97</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>7</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>148</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>MTQPLSAYFINSSHNTYLTAGQLAGTSSVEMYRQALLWGCRCVELDVWKGRPPEEEPFITHGFTMTTEVPLRDVLEAIAETAFKTSPYPVILSFENHVDSAKQQAKMAEYCRSIFGDALLIEPLDKYPLAPGVPLPSPQDLMGRILVK</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>MDKPLSHYFIPSSHNTYLTGKQLWGESSVEGYIQALDAGCRCVELDCWDG--PDGEPVIYHGHTFTLPIKLSEVLEAIKDFAFVTSPYPVILSLENHC-SPDQQAKMAQMFKEIFGDMLYTPPLTSSLEV----LPSPEQLRGKILLK</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>M +PLS YFI SSHNTYLT  QL G SSVE Y QAL  GCRCVELD W G  P+ EP I HG T T  + L +VLEAI + AF TSPYPVILS ENH  S  QQAKMA+  + IFGD L   PL          LPSP+ L G+IL+K</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>9</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|270167</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd13361, PH_PLC_beta, Phospholipase C-beta (PLC-beta) pleckstrin homology (PH) domain.  PLC-beta (PLCbeta) is regulated by heterotrimeric G protein-coupled receptors through their C2 domain and long C-terminal extension which forms an autoinhibitory helix. There are four isoforms: PLC-beta1-4. The PH domain of PLC-beta2 and PLC-beta3 plays a dual role, much like PLC-delta1, by binding to the plasma membrane, as well as the interaction site for the catalytic activator. However, PLC-beta binds to the lipid surface independent of PIP2. PLC-beta1 seems to play unspecified roles in cellular proliferation and differentiation. PLC-beta consists of an N-terminal PH domain, a EF hand domain, a catalytic domain split into X and Y halves, a C2 domain and a C-terminal PDZ. Members of the Rho GTPase family (e.g., Rac1, Rac2, Rac3, and cdc42) have been implicated in their activation by binding to an alternate site on the N-terminal PH domain. A basic amino acid region within the enzyme&apos;s long C-terminal tail appears to function as a Nuclear Localization Signal for import into the nucleus. PLCs (EC 3.1.4.3) play a role in the initiation of cellular activation, proliferation, differentiation and apoptosis. They are central to inositol lipid signalling pathways, facilitating intracellular Ca2+ release and protein kinase C (PKC) activation. Specificaly, PLCs catalyze the cleavage of phosphatidylinositol-4,5-bisphosphate (PIP2) and result in the release of 1,2-diacylglycerol (DAG) and inositol 1,4,5-triphosphate (IP3). These products trigger the activation of protein kinase C (PKC) and the release of Ca2+ from intracellular stores. There are fourteen kinds of mammalian phospholipase C proteins which are are classified into six isotypes (beta, gamma, delta, epsilon, zeta, eta). PH domains have diverse functions, but in general are involved in targeting proteins to the appropriate cellular location or in the interaction with a binding partner. They share little sequence conservation, but all have a common fold, which is electrostatically polarized. Less than 10% of PH domains bind phosphoinositide phosphates (PIPs) with high affinity and specificity. PH domains are distinguished from other PIP-binding domains by their specific high-affinity binding to PIPs with two vicinal phosphate groups: PtdIns(3,4)P2, PtdIns(4,5)P2 or PtdIns(3,4,5)P3 which results in targeting some PH domain proteins to the plasma membrane. A few display strong specificity in lipid binding. Any specificity is usually determined by loop regions or insertions in the N-terminus of the domain, which are not conserved across all PH domains. PH domains are found in cellular signaling proteins such as serine/threonine kinase, tyrosine kinases, regulators of G-proteins, endocytotic GTPases, adaptors, as well as cytoskeletal associated molecules and in lipid associated enzymes.the plasma membrane, but only a few (less than 10%) display strong specificity in binding inositol phosphates. Any specificity is usually determined by loop regions or insertions in the N-terminus of the domain, which are not conserved across all PH domains. PH domains are found in cellular signaling proteins such as serine/threonine kinases, tyrosine kinases, regulators of G-proteins, endocytotic GTPases, adaptors, cytoskeletal associated molecules, and in lipid associated enzymes.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>270167</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>127</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>139.813</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>351</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>2.87422e-40</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>12</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>138</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>1</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>126</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>70</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>89</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>1</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>127</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>LRRGSKFIKWDEETSSRNLVTLRVDPNGFFLYWTGPNMEVDTLDISSIRDTRTGRYARLPKDPKIREVLGFGGPDARLEEKLMTVVSGPDPVNTVFLNFMAVQDDTAKVWSEELFKLAMNILAQNAS</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>LLKGSKFDKWDEDSSLETPVTLKVDEYGFFLYWKSEGKETEVLDLSLIRDVRTGKYPKDPKDLKEREV-NVGGSDEDLEDRTLTIVSGTDLVNISFINFVAESEEVAKIWTEGLFKLAHNLLANNAS</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>L +GSKF KWDE++S    VTL+VD  GFFLYW     E + LD+S IRD RTG+Y + PKD K REV   GG D  LE++ +T+VSG D VN  F+NF+A  ++ AK+W+E LFKLA N+LA NAS</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>10</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|312695</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>pfam09279, EF-hand_like, Phosphoinositide-specific phospholipase C, efhand-like.  Members of this family are predominantly found in phosphoinositide-specific phospholipase C. They adopt a structure consisting of a core of four alpha helices, in an EF like fold, and are required for functioning of the enzyme.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>312695</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>85</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>45.4394</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>106</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>1.2767e-06</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>206</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>290</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>1</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>76</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>28</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>48</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>9</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>85</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>FLNKLCLRPDIDKILLEIGAKGKPYLTLEQLMDFINQKQRDPRLNEVLYPPLRPSQARLLIEKYEPNQQFLERDQMSMEGFSRYL</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>FYKMLTQREEIDRIFQEYSGDGQK-LSLDELVDFLREEQREEDAS--------PALALELIERYEPSETAKKQHAMTKDGFLMYL</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>F   L  R +ID+I  E    G+  L+L++L+DF+ ++QR+   +        P+ A  LIE+YEP++   ++  M+ +GF  YL</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>11</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|320036</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd16206, EFh_PRIP, EF-hand motif found in phospholipase C-related but catalytically inactive proteins (PRIP).  This family represents a class of metazoan phospholipase C related, but catalytically inactive proteins (PRIP), which belong to a group of novel inositol 1,4,5-trisphosphate (InsP3) binding protein. PRIP has a primary structure and domain architecture, incorporating a pleckstrin homology (PH) domain, four atypical EF-hand motifs, a PLC catalytic core domain with highly conserved X- and Y-regions split by a linker sequence, and a C-terminal C2 domain, similar to phosphoinositide-specific phospholipases C (PI-PLC, EC 3.1.4.11)-delta isoforms. Due to replacement of critical catalytic residues, PRIP do not have PLC enzymatic activity. PRIP consists of two subfamilies, PRIP-1(also known as p130 or PLC-L1), which is predominantly expressed in the brain, and PRIP-2 (also known as PLC-L2), which exhibits a relatively ubiquitous expression. Experiments show both, PRIP-1 and PRIP-2, are involved in InsP3-mediated calcium signaling pathway and GABA(A)receptor-mediated signaling pathway. In addition, PRIP-2 acts as a negative regulator of B-cell receptor signaling and immune responses.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>320036</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>143</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>45.8246</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>107</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>3.34848e-06</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>193</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>294</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>56</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>143</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>33</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>55</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>14</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>102</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>IRPDEFSLEIFERFLNKLCLRPDIDKILLEIGAKGKPYLTLEQLMDFINQKQRDPRLNEVLYPPLRPSQARLLIEKYEPNQQFLERDQMSMEGFSRYLGGEE</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>VSSDEF-VELF----KELATRPEIYFLLVRY-ASNKDYLTVDDLMLFLEAEQG--------MTGVTKEKCLEIINKYEPSEEGREKGQLGIDGFTRYLLSEE</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>+  DEF +E+F     +L  RP+I  +L+   A  K YLT++ LM F+  +Q            +   +   +I KYEP+++  E+ Q+ ++GF+RYL  EE</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>12</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|320032</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd16202, EFh_PI-PLCdelta, EF-hand motif found in phosphoinositide phospholipase C delta (PI-PLC-delta).  PI-PLC-delta isozymes represent a class of metazoan PI-PLCs that are some of the most sensitive to calcium among all PLCs. Their activation is modulated by intracellular calcium ion concentration, phospholipids, polyamines, and other proteins, such as RhoAGAP. Like other PI-PLC isozymes, PI-PLC-delta isozymes contain a core set of domains, including an N-terminal pleckstrin homology (PH) domain, four atypical EF-hand motifs, a PLC catalytic core, and a single C-terminal C2 domain. The PLC catalytic core domain is a TIM barrel with two highly conserved regions (X and Y) split by a highly degenerate linker sequence. There are three PI-PLC-delta isozymes (1, 3 and 4). PI-PLC-delta1 is relatively well characterized. It is activated by high calcium levels generated by other PI-PLC family members, and therefore functions as a calcium amplifier within the cell. Different PI-PLC-delta isozymes have different tissue distribution and different subcellular locations. PI-PLC-delta1 is mostly a cytoplasmic protein, PI-PLC-delta3 is located in the membrane, and PI-PLC-delta4 is predominantly detected in the cell nucleus. PI-PLC-delta isozymes is evolutionarily conserved even in non-mammalian species, such as yeast, slime molds and plants.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>320032</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>140</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>41.2022</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>95</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>0.000123187</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>187</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>290</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>42</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>136</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>28</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>53</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>9</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>104</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>FNRSESIRPDEFSLEIFERFLNKLCLRPDIDKILLEIGAKGKPYLTLEQLMDFINQKQRDPRLNEVLYPPLRPSQARLLIEKYEPNQQFLERDQMSMEGFSRYL</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>FQEADTSGEDVLDEEEFVQFYNRLTKRPEIEELFKKYSGDDEA-LTVEELRRFLQEEQK--------VKDVTLEWAEQLIETYEPSEDLKAQGLMSLDGFTLFL</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>F  +++   D    E F +F N+L  RP+I+++  +     +  LT+E+L  F+ ++Q+           +    A  LIE YEP++    +  MS++GF+ +L</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>13</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gnl|CDD|320029</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>cd15898, EFh_PI-PLC, EF-hand motif found in eukaryotic phosphoinositide-specific phospholipase C (PI-PLC, EC 3.1.4.11) isozymes.  PI-PLC isozymes are signaling enzymes that hydrolyze the membrane phospholipids phosphatidylinositol-4,5-bisphosphate (PIP2)  to generate two important second messengers in eukaryotic signal transduction cascades,  Inositol 1,4,5-trisphosphate (InsP3) and diacylglycerol (DAG). InsP3 triggers inflow of calcium from intracellular stores, while DAG, together with calcium, activates protein kinase C, which goes on to phosphorylate other molecules, leading to altered cellular activity. Calcium is required for the catalysis. This family corresponds to the four EF-hand motifs containing PI-PLC isozymes, including PI-PLC-beta (1-4), -gamma (1-2), -delta (1,3,4), -epsilon (1), -zeta (1), eta (1-2). Lower eukaryotes such as yeast and slime molds contain only delta-type isozymes. In contrast, other types of isoforms present in higher eukaryotes. This family also includes 1-phosphatidylinositol 4,5-bisphosphate phosphodiesterase 1 (PLC1) from fungi. Some homologs from plants contain only two atypical EF-hand motifs and they are not included. All PI-PLC isozymes except sperm-specific PI-PLC-zeta share a core set of domains, including an N-terminal pleckstrin homology (PH) domain, four atypical EF-hand motifs, a PLC catalytic core, and a single C2 domain. PI-PLC-zeta lacks the PH domain. The PLC catalytic core domain is a TIM barrel with two highly conserved regions (X and Y) split by a highly degenerate linker sequence. Most of EF-hand motifs found in PI-PLCs consist of a helix-loop-helix structure, but lack residues critical to metal binding. Moreover, the EF-hand region of most of PI-PLCs may have an important regulatory function, but it has yet to be identified. However, PI-PLC-zeta is a key exception. It is responsible for Ca2+ oscillations in fertilized oocytes and exhibits a high sensitivity to Ca2+ mediated through its EF-hand domain. In addition, PI-PLC-eta2 shows a canonical EF-loop directing Ca2+-sensitivity and thus can amplify transient Ca2+ signals. Also it appears that PI-PLC-delta1 can regulate the binding of PH domain to PIP2 in a Ca2+-dependent manner through its functionally important EF-hand domains. PI-PLCs can be activated by a variety of extracellular ligands, such as growth factors, hormones, cytokines and lipids. Their activation has been implicated in tumorigenesis and/or metastasis linked to migration, proliferation, growth, inflammation, angiogenesis and actin cytoskeleton reorganization.  PI-PLC-beta isozymes are activated by G-protein coupled receptor (GPCR) through different mechanisms. However, PI-PLC-gamma isozymes are activated by receptor tyrosine kinase (RTK), such as Rho and Ras GTPases. In contrast, PI-PLC-epsilon are activated by both GPCR and RTK. PI-PLC-delta1 and PLC-eta 1 are activated by GPCR-mediated calcium mobilization. The activation mechanism for PI-PLC-zeta remains unclear.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>320029</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>137</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>40.4318</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>93</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>0.000210271</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>142</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>290</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>1</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>133</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>39</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>72</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>20</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>151</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>FLRKAYTKLKLQVNQDGRIPVKNILKMFSADKKRVETALESCGLK--FNRSESIRPDEFSLEIFERFLNKLCLRPDIDKILLEIGAKGKPYLTLEQLMDFINQKQRDPRLNEVLYPPLRPSQARLLIEKYEPNQQFLERDQMSMEGFSRYL</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>WLRRQW--IKADKDGDGKLSLKEIKKLL----KRLNIRVSEKELKKLFKEVDTNGDGTLTFDEFEELYKSLTERPELEPIFKKYAGTNRDYMTLEEFIRFLREEQGE---------NVSEEECEELIEKYEPER---ENRQLSFEGFTNFL</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>+LR+ +  +K   + DG++ +K I K+     KR+   +    LK  F   ++      + + FE     L  RP+++ I  +     + Y+TLE+ + F+ ++Q +          +   +   LIEKYEP +   E  Q+S EGF+ +L</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
</Iteration_hits>
  <Iteration_stat>
    <Statistics>
      <Statistics_db-num>29480</Statistics_db-num>
      <Statistics_db-len>6494941</Statistics_db-len>
      <Statistics_hsp-len>96</Statistics_hsp-len>
      <Statistics_eff-space>1334009404</Statistics_eff-space>
      <Statistics_kappa>0.041</Statistics_kappa>
      <Statistics_lambda>0.267</Statistics_lambda>
      <Statistics_entropy>0.14</Statistics_entropy>
    </Statistics>
  </Iteration_stat>
</Iteration>
</BlastOutput_iterations>
</BlastOutput>

